a
啊阿呵吖嗄腌锕錒

ai
爱矮挨哎碍癌艾唉哀蔼隘埃皑呆嗌嫒瑷暧捱砹嗳锿霭乃剀呃噫奇阂乂伌僾儗凒剴叆呝啀嘊噯堨塧壒娭娾嬡嵦愛懓懝敱敳昹曖欬欸毐溰溾濭烠焥璦皚皧瞹硋磑礙絠薆藹諰譪譺賹躷醷鎄鑀閡阨阸隑靄靉餲馤騃鯦鱫鴱

an
按安暗岸俺案鞍氨胺厂广庵揞犴铵桉谙鹌埯黯干盒钳顸侒儑匼厈咹唵啽垵垾堓婩媕屽峖晻洝玵痷盦盫碪罯腤荌菴萻葊蓭裺誝諳豻貋遃鉗銨錌闇陰隂隌雸鞌韽頇頞馣鮟鴳鵪鶕

ang
昂肮盎仰卬岇昻枊醃醠骯

ao
袄凹傲奥熬懊敖翱澳嚣拗媪廒骜嗷坳遨聱螯獒鏊鳌鏖岙噢棍浇厫嗸嚻囂垇墺墽奡奧媼嫯岰嶅嶴慠扷抝摮擙柪梎泑滶澆澚熝爊獓璈眑磝磽礉翶翺芺蔜蝹襖謷謸軪郩鏕镺隞驁鰲鴁鴢鷔鼇

b

ba
把八吧爸拔罢跋巴芭扒坝霸叭靶笆疤耙捌粑茇岜鲅钯魃菝灞伯捭杷湃萆仈叐哱哵坺垻墢壩夿妭峇弝抜抪朳柭欛炦犮玐癹皅矲笩紦罷羓胈茷蚆覇詙豝跁軷釛釟鈀颰魞鮁鮊鲃鲌鼥

bai
百白摆败柏拜佰伯稗捭呗掰扒排派薜鞴唄庍拝挀擺敗栢猈竡粨粺絔薭襬贁鞁韛

ban
半办班般拌搬版斑板伴扳扮瓣颁绊癍坂钣舨阪瘢分彬豳辨辩並坢埿姅岅怑搫攽斒昄朌柈湴瓪秚籓粄絆肦蝂螁螌褩覂跘辦辧辬辯鈑鉡闆靽頒魬鳻

bang
帮棒绑磅镑邦榜蚌傍梆膀谤浜蒡彭旁纺螃並嗙垹埲塝嫎峀崗幇幚幫徬挷捠搒棓牓玤硥稖紡綁縍艕蚄蛖蜯謗邫鎊鞤騯髈

bao
包抱报饱保暴薄宝爆剥豹刨雹褒堡苞胞鲍炮瀑龅孢煲褓鸨趵葆勹呆簿袍裒宀曝佨儤剝勽嘐嚗堢報媬嫑寚寳寶忁怉曓枹珤砲窇笣緥菢蕔藵虣蚫袌裦襃賲鉋鑤铇闁靌靤飹飽駂骲髱鮑鳵鴇齙

be
萡

bei
被北倍杯背悲备碑卑贝辈钡焙狈惫臂褙悖蓓鹎鐾呗邶鞴孛陂碚俾埤怫波菩萆葡蜚跋俻偝偹備僃哱唄喺垻愂憊揹昁杮柸桮梖棑棓椑牬犕狽珼琲痺盃禙箃糒苝茀萯藣蛽襬誖諀貝軰輩鄁鉳鋇錍鐴骳鵯

ben
本奔苯笨夯锛贲畚坌体倴喯夲奙捹撪桳楍泍渀炃燌犇獖翉蟦賁輽逩錛鐼

beng
蹦绷甭崩迸蚌泵甏嘣俸傍唪堋平抨旁榜伻傰嗙埄埲塴奟嵭挷搒漨熢琣琫痭祊絣綳繃菶跰逬錋鏰镚閍鞛揼

bi
比笔闭鼻碧必避逼毕臂彼鄙壁蓖币弊辟蔽毙庇敝陛毖痹秘泌秕薜荸芘萆匕裨畀俾嬖狴筚箅篦舭荜襞庳铋跸吡愎贲滗濞璧哔髀弼妣婢仳佛卑埤复媲幅庀拂捭服枇檗殍波瞥纰脾虑被费跛鐾陂陴馥佊佖偪匂咇啚嗶坒堛夶奰妼娝嬶屄崥幣幤廦弻彃怭怶悂愊斃旇朼枈柀柲梐椑楅毴沘湢滭潷煏熚獘獙珌畁畐畢疕疪痺皀皕禆稫笓筆箃箄箆篳粃粊紕紴綼縪繴罷罼翍聛肶肸胇腗腷苾萞蓽蘗蜌螕袐襅襣觱詖诐豍貏貱費賁贔赑踾蹕躃躄邲鄨鄪鈚鉍錍鎞鏎鐴閇閈閉閟闬鞁鞞鞸韠飶饆馝駜驆髲魓魮鮅鮩鰏鲾鴓鵖鶝鷝鷩鸊鼊

bia
髟

bian
边变便遍编辩扁贬鞭卞辨辫忭砭匾汴碥蝙褊鳊笾苄窆弁缏煸封拚稹髟変峅徧惼抃揙昪汳炞牑猵獱甂疺稨箯籩糄編緶臱艑萹藊覍覵變豍貶辡辦辧辮辯邉邊邲釆鍽閞鞕頨鯾鯿鴘鶣

biao
表标彪膘杓婊飑飙鳔瘭飚镳裱骠镖剽嫖漂灬苞鏖髟俵僄儦墂幖徱摽標檦淲滮瀌熛爂猋穮篻脿膔臕蔈藨褾諘謤贆錶鏢鑣颮颷飆飇飈飊驃驫骉鰾麃

bie
别憋鳖瘪蹩扒拔捌撇秘蔽別咇彆徶撆柭柲猰癟穪苾莂虌蛂蟞襒鱉鼈龞

bin
宾濒摈彬斌滨豳膑殡缤髌傧槟鬓镔玢份浜频儐擯椕殯氞汃濱濵瀕瑸璸砏繽臏虨蠙訜豩賓賔贇赟邠鑌霦頻顮髕髩鬂鬢

bing
并病兵冰丙饼屏秉柄炳摒槟禀邴冫平拼枋燹绠疒並仌併倂偋傡垪寎幷庰怲抦掤昞昺栟栤梹棅檳氷燷琕痭癛癝眪稟窉竝絣綆苪蛃誁跰鈵鉼鋲陃靐鞆鞞鞸餅餠鮩

bo
拨波播泊博伯驳玻剥薄勃菠钵搏脖帛般柏舶渤铂箔膊魄卜礴跛檗亳鹁踣啵蕃簸钹饽擘佛募孛怕拍拔擗暴服泼潘瀑爆番白百簿艴菩蒲薜蘖趵跑鲅掰仢侼僠僰剝哱噃嚗壆妭孹嶓帗彴愽懪挬撥柭桲榑檘欂殕浡淿湐潑煿牔犦犻狛猼瓝瓟癶發皪盋砵碆磻礡秡穛笩箥簙糪紴缽肑胉艊苩茀茷葧蔔蔢蘗蚾袚袯袹襎襏襮詙譒豰蹳郣鈸鉑鉢鋍鎛鑮镈餑餺馎馛馞駁駮驋髆髉鮁鮊鱍鲌鵓

bu
不步补布部捕卜簿哺堡埠怖埔瓿逋晡钸钚醭卟拊溥薄附鞴佈僕勏吥咘埗婄尃峬庯廍悑抪捗捬撲擈柨歨歩獛秿箁篰荹蔀補誧踄輹轐郶鈈鈽陠餔餢鯆鳪鵏鸔

c

ca
擦拆礤嚓蔡傪囃攃橴磣礸遪

cai
才菜采材财裁猜踩睬蔡彩倸偲啋埰婇寀戝扐採揌棌綵縩纔財跴

can
蚕残掺参惨惭餐灿骖璨孱黪粲傪儏參叄叅喰嘇噆囋嬠嬱嵾慘慙慚憯戔摲朁殘淺湌澯燦爘穇篸薒蝅蠶蠺謲蹔鏒飡飱驂鯵鰺鲹黲

cang
藏仓沧舱苍伧臧仺倉傖凔匨嵢欌滄濸獊瑲篬罉艙蒼蔵螥賶鑶鶬鸧

cao
草操曹槽糙嘈艚螬漕屮澡艹造傮嶆愺慅慒懆撡曺肏艸蓸褿襙鄵鏪鐰騲鼜

ce
册侧策测厕恻帻栅赦刂側冊厠墄嫧幘廁惻憡拺敇柵測畟笧筞筴箣簎粣荝萗萴蓛齰

cen
参岑涔參叄叅嵾梣汵硶穇笒篸膥

ceng
曾层蹭噌僧增缯層嶒橧竲繒驓

ch

cha
查插叉茶差岔搽察茬碴刹诧楂槎镲衩汊馇檫姹杈锸嚓土捷接斜猹苴荼钗喳仛侘偛剎嗏垞奼岎嵖扠扱挿捈揷摖査梌疀秅紁肞臿艖芆荖褨訍詧詫蹅釵銟鍤鎈鑔靫餷

chai
柴拆差豺钗瘥虿侪叉搓查茈龇儕勑喍囆扠犲祡茝蔕蠆袃訍釵齜

chan
产缠掺搀阐颤铲谗蝉单馋觇婵蒇谄冁廛孱蟾羼镡忏潺禅骣躔澶兔厘嬗崭掸沾渐胀苫裣谶丳亶佔僝僤儃儳兎刬剗剷劖単啴單嘽嚵囅團墠壥嬋嵼嶃嶄巉幝幨憚懴懺摌摲摻撣攙斺旵梴棎榐欃毚浐湹滻漸潹瀍瀺灛煘燀獑產産硟磛禪簅緂緾繟繵纏纒脠艬蕆螹蟬蟺袩裧襌襜襝覘誗諂譂讇讒讖蹍辿鄽酁醦鉆鋋鋓鏟鑱镵閳闡韂顫饞

chang
长唱常场厂尝肠畅昌敞倡偿猖裳鲳氅菖惝嫦徜鬯阊怅伥昶苌娼倘尚淌仧倀僘償儻兏厰嘗嚐場塲尙廠悵晿暢棖椙淐焻玚琩瑒瑺瓺甞畼脹腸膓萇蟐裮誯鋹鋿錩鏛锠長镸閶闛韔鯧鱨鲿鼚

chao
朝抄超吵潮巢炒嘲剿绰钞怊焯耖晁唠涛绉绍诌仦仯劋勦嘮巐巣弨摷槱樔欩漅濤焣煼牊眧窲粆紹綤綽縐繛罺觘訬謅謿趠趫轈鄛鈔麨鼂鼌

che
车撤扯掣彻尺澈坼砗多宅屮斥池伡俥偖勶呫唓喢夛奲徹揊摰撦烢烲焎爡瞮硨硩聅莗蛼詀謵車迠頙

chen
趁称辰臣尘晨沉陈衬橙忱郴榇抻谌碜谶宸龀嗔伧琛堪填帘枕沈湛疹眈缜肜胂闯秤侲傖儭嚫塡塵墋夦愖捵揨敐曟桭棧棽樄櫬瀋烥煁疢瘎瘨瞋硶磣稱綝縝茞莀莐蔯薼螴襯訦諃諶謓謲讖賝贂趂趻跈踸軙迧醦鈂鍖闖陳霃鷐麎齓齔

cheng
成乘盛撑称城程呈诚惩逞骋澄橙承塍柽埕铖噌铛酲晟裎枨蛏丞瞠伥净呛嵊徵抢敞樘浈盯趟蹦郢醒秤乗侱倀偁僜嗆埩堘塖娍宬峸庱徎徴悜憆憕懲挰掁搶摚摤撐撜朾棖棦椉槍橕橖檉檙氶泟洆浧浾淨溗澂瀓瀞爯牚珵珹琤瑲畻睈矃碀稱穪窚竀筬絾緽脀脭荿虰蟶觕誠赪赬踜郕鋮鎗鏳鏿鐺阷靗頳饓騁騬鯎黨

chi
吃尺迟池翅痴赤齿耻持斥侈弛驰炽匙踟坻茌墀饬媸豉褫敕哧瘛蚩啻鸱眵螭篪魑叱彳笞嗤傺哆啸喜她抬拆拖提搋柢沱治滞眙离移胝芪茬莉蛇踅饰骊郗佁侙俿剟勅卙卶叺呎呬呮呹喫嘨嘯噄噭坘垑奓妛屟岻彨彲徲恜恥慗慸憏懘扡抶拕拸捇摛摴攡杘柅樆欼歗歭歯汖沶泜淔湁滯漦灻烾熾狋瓻痓痸瘈癡瞝祇竾筂箈箎粚糦絺翄翤翨耛肔胣胵脪腟荎菭蚇蚳蝭袲袳裭訵誀誃誺謘謻貾赿趍趐趩跅跢跮踶軧迡迣遅遟遫遲邌鉓鉹銐鍉離雴飭飾餝饎馳騺驪鳷鴟鵄鵣鶒鶗鶙鷘麶黐齒齝

chong
冲重虫充宠崇涌种艟忡舂铳憧茺僮潼烛盅茧酮偅傭喠嘃埫寵崈徸憃揰摏樁沖浺漴爞珫痋祌種緟罿翀蝩蟲衝褈蹖蹱銃隀

chou
抽愁臭仇丑稠绸酬筹踌畴瞅惆俦帱瘳雠圳妯扭揄溴诌钮鲋丒侴偢儔吜嚋婤媿嬦幬怞懤掫搊擣杻杽栦椆檮殠燽牰犨犫畤疇皗盩眣矁篘籌紬絒綢臰菗薵裯詶謅譸讎讐诪跾躊遚酧醔醜醻鈕雔魗鮘鯈

chu
出处初锄除触橱楚础储畜滁矗搐躇厨雏楮杵刍怵绌亍憷蹰黜蜍樗助柠涂淑硫祝絮著褚诎诸屮俶傗儊儲処嘼埱媰岀幮廚慉懨拀摢摴敊斶椘榋槒橻檚櫉櫖櫥欪歜滀濋炪犓珿琡璴礎禇竌竐篨絀耝耡臅芻菆蒢蒭蓫蕏藸處蟵蠩觕觸詘諔諸豖豠貙趎跦踀踰躕鄐鉏鋤閦雛鶵鸀齣齭齼

chua
撮欻歘

chuai
揣膪啜嘬搋踹欼腄膗

chuan
穿船传串川喘椽氚遄钏舡舛巛惴掾踹镩傳僢剶圌堾暷歂汌猭玔瑏甎篅膞舩荈賗踳輲釧鶨

chuang
窗床闯创疮幢怆仓囱舂葱仺倉傸刅刱剏剙創噇囪愴戧摐朣橦漴漺牀牎牕瘡磢窓窻膧蔥闖

chui
吹垂炊锤捶椎槌棰陲倕圌埀惙搥桘箠腄菙郵錘鎚顀鬌魋龡

chun
春唇纯蠢醇淳椿蝽莼鹑朐沌肫辁偆僢堾媋惷旾暙杶楯槆橁櫄浱湻滣漘犉瑃睶箺純胊脣膞芚萅萶蒓蓴賰踳輇輴醕錞陙鯙鰆鶉鶞

chuo
戳绰踔啜龊辍促斫淖焯簇缀荃蔟趵踱躇辶醛镞吷嚽娕娖婥婼孎惙拺擉歠涰磭箹綴綽繛腏趠跿輟辵逴酫鋜錣鏃鑡齪齱

ci
次此词瓷慈雌磁辞刺茨伺疵赐差兹呲鹚祠糍厕司嵯措柴滋粢茈荠蚝螅趑佌佽偨刾厠呰啙垐堲姕嬨嵳庛廁朿枱柌栜栨泚澬濨玼珁甆皉礠絘縒胔茦茲莿萕薋薺蛓螆蠀詞賜赼趀跐辝辤辭鈶飺餈骴髊鮆鴜鶿鷀齹

cong
从丛葱匆聪囱琮枞淙璁骢苁偬窗纵叢囪婃孮従徖從忩怱悤悰慒憁暰棇楤樅樬樷欉漎漗潀潈潨灇焧熜燪爜瑽瞛碂篵総緫縦縱總繱聡聦聰茐菆蓯蔥藂蟌誴謥賨賩鏦騘驄

cou
凑楱辏腠奏揍族簇蔟薮趋趣湊玼藪趨輳

cu
粗醋簇促卒徂猝蔟蹙酢殂蹴且戚绉趋趣错卆噈娕娖媨怚憱捽瘄瘯皻縐縬脨蔍蔖觕誎趗趥趨踀踓踤踧蹵錯顣麁麄麆麤鼀

cuan
窜蹿篡攒汆爨镩撺昕僔巑攅攛攢櫕欑殩濽灒熶穳窾竄篹簒菆襸躥鋑鑹

cui
催脆摧翠崔淬衰瘁粹璀啐悴萃毳榱体察隹乼伜倅凗啛墔崒崪嶉忰慛椊槯漼濢焠熣獕琗疩皠磪竁粋紣綷縗繀缞翆脃脺膬膵臎襊趡踤鏙顇

cun
村寸存蹲忖皴浚侟刌吋墫拵洊澊竴籿踆邨

cuo
错撮搓挫措磋嵯厝鹾脞痤蹉瘥锉矬摧昔最躜剉剒夎嵳庴棤澨營瑳睉縒莝莡蒫蓌蔖虘襊諎躦逪遳酂酇醝銼錯髊鹺齹

d

da
大答达打搭瘩塔笪耷哒褡疸怛靼妲沓嗒鞑塌胆迭亣剳匒呾咑噠垯墶憚搨撘橽毼汏溚炟燵畗畣眔矺笚繨羍荅荙薘蟽觰詚跶躂迏迖逹達鎉鎝鐽韃龖龘

dai
带代呆戴待袋逮歹贷怠傣大殆呔玳迨岱甙黛骀绐埭棣毒诒逯隶驮侢叇嘚垈帒帯帶廗懛曃柋汏瀻獃瑇箉簤紿緿艜蔕蚮蝳螮襶詒貸跢蹛軑軚軩轪遞遰霴靆馱駄駘鮘鴏黱

dan
但单蛋担弹掸胆淡丹耽旦氮诞郸惮石疸澹瘅萏殚眈聃箪赕儋啖冉坛忱怛憾檐湛潭澶膻蜒觇詹赡卩亻丼亶伔倓僤儃冄刐勯匰単呾唌啗啿單嘾噉噡嚪壇妉娊媅帎弾彈惔愖憚憺抌撢撣擔柦欿殫沊泹澸燀狚玬瓭甔疍癉癚皽砃禫窞簞紞繵耼聸腅膽蜑蟺衴褝襌襜覘觛訑誕譂贉贍蹛躭鄲酖醈霮頕餤饏馾駳髧鴠黕黮黵蓞

dang
当党挡档荡谠铛宕菪凼裆砀场烫偒儅噹圵垱場壋婸崵嵣愓擋攩檔欓氹潒澢灙燙珰瑒璗璫瓽當瘍盪瞊碭礑筜簜簹艡蕩蘯蟷襠譡讜趤逿鐺闣雼黨

dao
到道倒刀岛盗稻捣悼导蹈祷帱纛忉焘氘叨俦受啁忑惆洮涛陶鸟刂儔嘄噵壔宲導屶島嶋嶌嶹幬捯搗擣朷椡槝檤檮濤燾瓙盜禂禱稲箌絩翢翿舠菿薵虭衜衟裯軇醻釖陦隝隯魛鱽鳥

de
的地得德底锝登陟嘚徳恴悳惪棏淂鍀

dei
得哋

den
扥扽

deng
等灯邓登澄瞪凳蹬磴镫噔嶝戥簦橙僜墱嬁憕櫈燈璒竳艠覴豋鄧鐙隥

di
地第底低敌抵滴帝递嫡弟缔堤的涤提笛迪狄翟蒂觌邸谛诋嘀柢骶羝氐棣睇娣荻碲镝坻籴砥勺啻杓约胝芍莜蹄逐逮隶题仾俤偙僀儥厎呧唙啇啲嚁坔坘埅埊埞墆墑墬奃媂嵽嶳廸弔弚弤彽怟慸扚拞掋揥摕敵旳杕枤梊梑楴樀浟渧滌焍牴玓珶甋疐眱碮磾祶禘篴糴約締聜肑腣苐苖菂菧蓧蔋蔐蔕藋藡蚳蝃螮袛覿觝詆諟諦豴赿趆踧踶蹏蹢軧逓遞適遰釱鉪鍉鏑阺隄靮鞮頔題馰髢鬄魡鯳鸐

dia
嗲

dian
点电店殿淀掂颠垫碘惦奠典佃靛滇甸踮钿坫阽癫簟玷巅癜埝拈沾涎蜓丶佔傎厧唸墊壂奌婝婰嵮巓巔扂攧敁敟椣槇槙橂橝湺澱琔痶瘨癲磹腍蒧蕇蜔詀蹎鈿電頕顚顛驔點齻

diao
掉钓叼吊雕调刁碉凋鸟铞铫鲷貂佻倜刀挑稠粜绸莜蜩赵跳踔轺骠伄刟奝嬥屌弔弴彫扚椆殦汈淍琱瘹瞗矵窎窵竨簓糶絩綢蓧藋虭蛁訋誂調趙軺釣鈟銱鋽錭鑃雿颩魡鮉鯛鳥鳭鵃鵰鸼鼦

die
爹跌叠碟蝶迭谍牒堞瓞揲蹀耋鲽垤喋佚涉渫窒至褶踢轶鳎踮咥哋啑峌崼嵽幉怢恎惵戜挃挕昳曡柣楪槢殜氎泆渉牃畳疂疉疊眣眰絰绖耊胅臷艓苵蜨螲褋褺詄諜趃跕跮蹛軼鐡鐵镻鞢鮙鰈鰨

ding
顶定盯订叮丁钉鼎锭町玎铤腚碇疔仃耵酊啶奠汀灯葶奵嵿帄忊掟椗濎甼矴碠磸聢艼萣薡虰訂釘鋌錠鐤靪頂顁飣饤鼑

diu
丢铥丟銩颩

dong
动东懂洞冻冬董栋侗恫峒鸫垌胨胴硐氡岽咚桐甬筒酮夂倲働凍動勭埬墥姛娻嬞峝崠崬戙挏揰昸東棟氭涷湩烔燑狫笗筩箽絧腖苳菄蕫蝀衕詷諌迵霘駧騆鮗鯟鶇鶫鼕

dou
都斗豆逗陡抖痘兜读蚪窦篼蔸投渎窬逾酡钭乧侸兠凟剅吺唗斣枓梪橷毭氀浢瀆瞗竇脰艔荳讀郖酘鈄鋀閗闘阧餖饾鬥鬦鬪鬬鬭唞

du
读度毒渡堵独肚镀赌睹杜督都犊妒顿蠹笃嘟渎椟牍黩髑芏土宅橐竺纛诧锗儥凟剢剫匵厾噣塗妬嬻帾斁晵暏樚樞櫝殬殰涜瀆牘犢獨琽瓄皾睪秺竇笁篤荰蝳螙蠧裻襡襩覩詫読讀讟豄賭贕醏錖鍍鍺鑟闍阇陼靯韇韣韥頓騳黷

duan
段短断端锻缎椴煅簖彖踹偳剬塅媏斷毈瑖碫篅籪緞耑腶葮褍躖鍛鍴

dui
对队堆兑敦镦碓怼憝夺追锐兊兌垖埻塠奪対對嵟憞懟搥杸濧濻瀢瀩痽磓祋綐膭薱謉譈譵鈗銳鋭錞鎚鐓鐜陮隊頧鴭

dun
吨顿蹲墩敦钝盾囤遁不趸沌盹镦礅炖砘俊豚伅噸墪壿庉忳惇憞撉撴楯橔潡燉犜獤碷腞腯蜳踲蹾躉逇遯鈍鐓鐜頓驐

duo
多朵夺舵剁垛跺惰堕掇哆驮度躲踱沲咄铎裰哚缍兑捶揣杂柁棰沱郸锗陀隋亸仛兊兌凙刴剟剫吋喥嚉嚲垜埵墮墯夛奪奲媠嫷尮崜嶞憜挅挆敓敚敠敪朶杕枤柂柮桗椯橢毲沰澤痥硾綞茤袳詑誃貀趓跢跥跿躱軃鄲鈬錞鍺鐸陊陏隓飿饳馱駄鬌鮵鵽點

e
饿哦额鹅蛾扼俄讹阿遏峨娥恶厄鄂锇谔垩锷阏萼苊轭婀莪鳄颚腭愕呃噩鹗屙亚伪侉哑啊啐垭庵曷歹硪胺邑隘鬲亜亞佮偔偽僞僫匎匼卾吪呝咢咹唖啈啞噁囐囮埡堊堨堮妸妿姶娾娿媕屵岋峉峩崿廅悪惡戹搕搤搹擜枙椏櫮欸歞歺洝涐湂玀珴琧痷皒睋砈砐砨砵硆磀礘蒍蕚蘁蚅蝁覨訛詻誐諤譌讍豟軛軶輵迗遌遻鈋鋨鍔鑩閜閼阨阸頞頟額顎餓餩騀魤魥鰐鰪鱷鴳鵈鵝鵞鶚齃齶齾鈪

ei
诶欸

en
恩摁蒽嗯唔奀峎煾饐

eng
鞥

er
而二耳儿饵尔贰洱珥鲕鸸佴迩铒濡侕児兒刵咡唲嬭尒尓峏弍弐杒栭栮樲毦洏渪爾粫耏聏胹臑荋薾衈袻誀貮貳趰輀輭轜邇鉺陑陾隭餌駬髵髶鮞鴯乻

f

fa
发法罚伐乏筏阀珐垡砝拔拨泛贬佱傠姂廢彂撥栰橃汎沷灋琺疺発發瞂笩罰罸茷蕟藅貶醗醱鍅閥髪髮

fan
反饭翻番犯凡帆返泛繁烦贩范樊藩矾钒燔蘩畈蕃蹯梵幡拚蟠袢攵犭仮伋凢凣勫匥噃墦奿婏嬎嬏嬔忛憣払旙旛杋柉棥楓橎氾汎渢滼瀪瀿煩犿璠畨盕礬笲笵範籓籵緐繙羳膰舤舧舩薠蠜襎訉販軓軬轓辺釩鐇颿飜飯飰鱕鷭

fang
放房防纺芳方访仿坊妨肪钫彷邡枋舫鲂匚倣埅堏旊昉昘昞汸淓牥瓬眆眪祊紡蚄訪趽鈁錺雱髣魴鰟鳑鴋鶭

fei
非飞肥费肺废匪吠沸菲诽啡篚蜚腓扉妃斐狒芾悱镄霏翡榧淝鲱绯痱怫拂砩祓绋茇裴俷剕厞墢奜婓婔屝廃廢昲暃曊朏杮柹棐橃橨櫠渄濷犻猆琲疿癈笰紼緋胇胏胐茀萉蕜蕟蕡蜰蟦裵裶襏誹費鐨陫靅靟飛飝餥馡騑騛髴鯡鼣鼥

fen
分份芬粉坟奋愤纷忿粪酚焚吩氛汾棼瀵鲼玢偾鼢匪喷奔愍扮拚燔盼贲颁僨噴坆坋墳奮妢岎帉幩弅憤敃昐朆朌枌梤棻橨歕濆炃燌燓獖瞓砏秎竕糞紛羒羵翂肦膹葐蒶蕡蚠蚡衯訜豮豶賁躮轒鈖錀鐼隫雰頒餴饙馚馩魵鱝鳻黂黺鼖

feng
风封逢缝蜂丰枫疯冯奉讽凤峰锋烽砜俸酆葑沣唪捧泛蚌逄鹏仹偑僼凨凬凮埄堸夆妦寷峯崶捀摓桻楓檒沨浲渢湗溄漨灃炐焨煈熢犎猦琒甮瘋盽碸篈綘縫肨舽艂莑蘕蘴覂諷豊豐賵赗鄷鋒鎽鏠靊風飌馮鳯鳳鴌鵬麷

fiao
覅

fo
佛仏仸坲梻

fou
否缶不垺妚炰紑缹缻芣衃雬鴀

fu
副幅扶浮富福负伏付复服附俯斧赴缚拂夫父符孵敷赋辅府腐腹妇抚覆辐肤氟佛俘傅讣弗涪袱市甫釜脯腑阜咐黼砩苻趺跗蚨芾鲋幞茯滏蜉拊菔蝠鳆蝮绂绋赙罘稃匐麸凫桴莩孚馥驸怫祓呋郛芙艴黻不仅包呒哺宓彳怀掊沸溥莆费还锫阝鞴乀伕俌俛偩偪冨冹刜咈哹嘸坿垘垺報妋姇娐婏婦媍嬎嬔尃岪峊巿帗弣彿復怤懯抙捊捬撫旉枎枹柎柫柭栿棴椨椱榑汱沕泭洑澓炥烰焤玞玸琈璷甶畉畐畗癁盙砆祔禣秿稪竎笰筟箁箙簠粰糐紨紱紼絥綍綒緮縛纀罦翇胕膚艀芣茀荂荴萉萯葍蓲蕧虙蚥蚹蛗蜅蝜衭袚袝複褔襆襥覄訃詂諨豧負費賦賻踾軵輔輹輻邚邞郍郙鄜酜酻釡鈇鉘鉜錇鍑鍢陚韍韛韨頫颫颰駙髴鬴鮄鮒鮲鰒鳧鳬鳺鴔鵩鶝麩麬麱

fui
猤

g

ga
噶胳夹嘎咖轧钆伽旮尬尕尜呷嘠玍軋釓錷魀

gai
该改盖概钙芥溉戤垓丐陔赅咳核汽胲阂骸乢侅匃匄姟峐忋摡晐杚槩槪漑瓂畡磑祴絠絯荄葢蓋該豥賅賌郂鈣鎅閡阣隑

gan
赶干感敢竿甘肝柑杆赣秆旰酐矸疳泔苷擀绀橄澉淦尴坩个乾奸捍汗乹亁仠佄倝凎凲咁尲尶尷幹忓扞攼桿榦檊汵浛漧灨玕玵皯盰稈笴筸篢簳粓紺芉虷衦詌諴豃贑贛趕迀釬錎飦骭魐鰔鱤鳡鳱

gang
刚钢纲港缸岗杠冈肛扛筻罡戆亢伉抗肮颃冮剛堈堽岡崗戅戇掆棡槓溝焵牨犅犺疘矼碙綱罁罓釭鋼鎠阬頏

gao
高搞告稿膏篙羔糕镐皋郜诰杲缟睾槔锆槁藁咎浩蒿勂吿夰峼暠槀槹橰檺櫜滜澔獋獔皐睪祮祰禞稁稾筶縞羙臯菒藳誥鋯鎬韟餻髙鷎鷱鼛

ge
个各歌割哥搁格阁隔革咯胳葛蛤戈鸽疙盖屹合铬硌骼颌袼塥虼圪镉仡舸鬲嗝膈搿纥哿介可噶浩砝菏钾铪闸髂佫佮個匌吤呄嘅嘢彁愅戓戨扢挌擱敋杚槅櫊滆滒澔牫牱犵猲獦秴箇紇肐臈臵茖蓋蛒裓觡詥諽謌輵轕鉀鉻鉿鎑鎘鎶閘閣閤鞈鞷韐韚頜騔魺鮥鮯鰪鲄鴐鴚鴿鵅

gei
给給

gen
跟根哏茛亘艮痕揯搄

geng
更耕颈梗耿庚羹埂赓鲠哽绠亢硬邢亙刯堩峺恆挭掶暅椩浭焿畊絙絚綆緪縆羮莄菮賡郉郠頸骾鯁鶊鹒

go
嗰

gong
工公功共弓攻宫供恭拱贡躬巩汞龚红肱觥珙蚣咣廾杠虹蛩赣匑匔厷唝嗊塨宮幊愩慐拲杛栱渱熕碽篢糼紅羾觵貢贑贛躳輁銾鞏髸魟龏龔

gou
够沟狗钩勾购构苟垢句岣彀枸鞲觏缑笱诟遘媾篝佝区拘鸲傋冓區呴坸夠姤抅搆撀構泃溝煹玽簼緱耇耈耉茩蚼袧褠覯訽詬豰豿購軥鈎鉤雊韝鮈鴝鸜

gu
古股鼓谷故孤箍姑顾固雇估咕骨辜沽蛊贾菇梏鸪汩轱崮菰鹄鹘钴臌酤呱鲴诂牯瞽毂锢牿痼觚蛄罟嘏告哌枯滑瓠皋胍苦角骰傦僱凅劷唂唃啒嗀嗗堌夃嫴尳峠崓怘愲扢抇柧棝榖榾橭櫎泒淈濲瀔焸皷盬硲磆祻稒穀笟箛篐糓縎罛羖脵臯苽蓇薣蛌蠱詁賈軱軲轂逧鈲鈷錮頋顧餶馉鮕鯝鴣鵠鶻鼔皼

gua
挂刮瓜寡剐褂卦呱胍鸹栝诖惴舌括冎剮劀叧咶咼啩坬掛歄焻煱絓緺罣罫苽詿諣趏踻銛銽铦颪颳騧鴰

guai
怪拐乖掴哙叏噲夬恠枴柺箉罫

guan
关管官观馆惯罐灌冠贯棺纶盥矜莞掼涫鳏鹳倌串斡果桄沦菅丱卝婠悹悺慣懽摜樌櫬權毌泴淉淪潅爟琯瓘痯瘝癏矔礶祼窤筦綸罆舘萖蒄覌観觀貫躀輨遦錧鏆鑵閞関闗關雚館鰥鱞鱹鳤鵍鸛

guang
光广逛桄犷咣胱恍扩横潢侊俇僙垙姯広廣挄撗擴櫎欟洸灮炗炚炛烡獷珖硄臦臩茪趪輄迋銧黆

gui
归贵鬼跪轨规硅桂柜龟诡闺瑰圭刽傀癸炔庋宄桧刿鳜鲑皈匦妫晷簋炅伪匮哇娃桅概沩洼祈绘觖蹶隗亀佹偽僞劊劌匭匱厬垝姽媯嫢嬀嶡嶲巂帰庪廆恑摫撌攰攱昋朹椝椢槣槶槻槼檜櫃櫰櫷歸氿湀溎潙珪璝瓌癐瞆瞡瞶硊祪禬窐筀簂絵繪胿膭茥蓕蘬蛫螝蟡袿襘規觤詭謉貴赽趹軌邽郌閨陒雟鞼騩鬶鬹鮭鱖鱥鳺鴂鴃龜

gun
滚棍辊鲧衮磙绲丨浑混锟鳏惃棞渾滾琯璭睔睴緄緷蓘蔉袞裷謴輥錕鮌鯀鰥

guo
过国果裹锅郭涡埚椁聒馘猓崞掴帼呙虢蜾蝈划唬囗搓枸活蜮蠃锞咶咼啯嘓囯囶囻圀國埻堝墎幗彉彍惈慖摑敋楇槨櫎淉渦漍濄瘑矌簂粿綶聝腂腘膕菓蔮蝸蟈褁輠過鈛錁鍋鐹餜馃

h

ha
哈蛤虾铪吓呵獬丷奤妎為蝦鉿

hai
还海害咳氦孩骇骸亥嗨醢胲咴阂颏嘿侅咍嗐嚡塰拸欬烸猲絯還郂酼閡頦餀饚駭駴

han
喊含汗寒汉旱酣韩焊涵函憨翰罕撼捍憾悍邯邗菡撖瀚阚顸蚶焓颔晗鼾厂嵌感旰泔淦滩澉甘矸轩钤仠佄傼兯凾厈咁哻唅嚂圅垾娢嫨屽崡嵅忓扞攼晘晥暵桿梒椷榦欦歛汵浛浫涆淊漢澏澣灘熯爳猂琀甝皔睅笒筨糮肣莟蔊蘫虷蛿蜬蜭螒譀谽豃軒釬鈐銲鋎鋡閈闞闬雗靬韓頇頜頷顄顩馠馯駻鬫魽鳱鶾

hang
行巷航夯杭吭颃沆绗珩桁炕狼肮酐垳妔忼斻笐筕絎苀蚢貥迒邟頏魧

hao
好号浩嚎壕郝毫豪耗貉镐昊颢灏嚆蚝嗥皓蒿濠薅唬妞皋睾傐儫呺哠嘷噑恏悎昦晧暠暤暭曍椃淏滈滜澔灝獆獋皜皞皡皥秏竓籇翯聕膠臯茠薃薧藃號虠蠔諕譹鄗鎒鎬鐞顥鰝

he
和喝合河禾核何呵荷贺赫褐盒鹤菏貉阂涸吓嗬劾盍翮阖颌壑诃纥曷呙呼哈嗑害揭格洽渴硅缴苛藿蚵蝎辂辖阋霍鹄佫咊咼哬啝喛嗃噈嚇垎姀寉峆惒愒抲挌敆柇楁欱毼渇渮湼澕焃煂熆熇燺爀犵狢癋皬盇盉碋礉秴篕籺粭紇繳翯萂藃螛蠚袔覈訶訸詥謞貈賀輅轄郃鉌鑉閡闔隺靍靎靏鞨頜餄餲饸鬩魺鲄鵠鶡鶮鶴鸖鹖麧齃齕龁龢

hei
黑嗨嘿嬒潶黒

hen
很狠恨痕哏掀艮佷噷拫詪鞎

heng
横恒哼衡亨行桁珩蘅訇佷啈堼姮恆悙橫涥烆狟胻脝鑅鴴鵆鸻

ho
乊

hong
红轰哄虹洪宏烘鸿弘讧訇蕻闳薨黉荭泓汪港仜厷叿吰吽哅唝嗊嚝垬妅娂宖屸巆彋愩揈撔晎汯浤浲渱渹潂澋澒灴焢玒玜瓨硔硡竑竤篊粠紅紘紭綋纮羾翃翝耾舼苰葒葓訌謍谹谼谾軣輷轟鈜鉷銾鋐鍧閎閧闀闂霐霟鞃鬨魟鴻黌

hou
后厚吼喉侯候猴鲎篌堠後逅糇骺瘊诟吽呴垕帿洉犼睺矦翭翵腄葔詬豞郈鄇銗鍭餱鮜鯸鱟鲘齁

hu
湖户呼虎壶互胡护糊弧忽狐蝴葫沪乎戏核和瑚唬鹕冱怙鹱笏戽扈鹘浒祜醐琥囫烀轷瓠煳斛鹄猢惚岵滹觳唿槲汩羽胍芦芴苦虍许钴雇乕俿冴匢匫喖嗀嗃嘑嘝嚛垀壷壺姱婟媩嫭嫮寣帍幠弖怘恗戯戱戲戶戸抇搰摢擭昈昒曶枑楛楜槴歑殻汻沍泘洿淈淲淴滬滸濩瀫焀熩瓡瓳礐穫箎箶簄粐絗綔縎縏縠膴舗芐芔苸萀蔛蔰虖虝螜衚觷許謼護豰軤鄠鈷鋘錿鍙鍸隺雐雽韄頀頶餬鬍魱鯱鰗鱯鳠鳸鴩鵠鶘鶦鶮鶻鸌

hua
话花化画华划滑哗猾豁铧桦骅砉侉劐哇学找敌浍稞鲑劃吪嘩埖姡婲婳嫿嬅學崋搳摦撶杹椛槬樺檴澅澮獪璍畫畵硴磆粿糀繣腂舙芲華蒍蕐蘤蘳螖觟話誮諙諣譁譮輠釪釫鋘錵鏵驊魤鮭鷨黊夻

huai
坏怀淮槐徊划踝喟圳坯佪咶嘳壊壞懐懷櫰瀤耲蘹蘾褢褱

huan
换还唤环患缓欢幻宦涣焕豢桓痪漶獾擐逭鲩郇鬟寰奂锾圜洹萑缳浣垸援灌瑗皖眩脘鹳喚喛嚾圂堚奐孉寏峘嵈巜愌懁懽換攌梙槵欥歓歡汍渙潅澣澴烉煥犿狟瑍環瓛瘓睆睔瞏瞣糫絙綄緩繯羦肒荁萈蒝藧螌蠸讙豩豲貆貛輐轘還酄鉮鍰鐶镮闤阛雈雚驩鯇鯶鰀鴅鵍鸛鹮

huang
黄慌晃荒簧凰皇谎惶蝗磺恍煌幌隍肓潢篁徨鳇遑癀湟蟥璜芒茫偟兤喤堭塃墴奛媓宺崲巟怳愰揘晄曂朚楻榥櫎汻洸滉炾熀熿爌獚瑝皝皩穔縨艎葟衁詤諻謊趪鍠鎤鐄锽韹餭騜鰉鱑鷬黃

hui
回会灰绘挥汇辉毁悔惠晦徽恢秽慧贿蛔讳徊卉烩诲彗浍珲蕙喙恚哕晖隳麾诙蟪茴洄咴虺荟缋堕桧涣皓眭睢虫违韦溃佪僡儶匯叀嘒噅噕噦嚖囘囬圚墮壞婎媈孈寭屷幑廆廻廽彙彚徻恛恵憓懳拻揮撝暉暳會椲楎槥橞檅檓檜櫘毀毇沬泋洃湏滙潓澮濊瀈灳烜烠烣煇煒燬燴獩琿璤璯痐瘣睳瞺禈穢篲絵繢繪翙翚翬翽芔蒐蔧薈薉藱蘬蘳蚘蛕蜖螝袆褘襘詯詼誨諱譓譭譮譿豗賄輝輠迴逥違銊鏸鐬闠阓隓靧鞼韋韢頮顪餯鮰鰴鼿齀

hun
混昏荤浑婚魂阍珲馄溷诨挥捆昆棍绲缗俒倱圂婫忶惛惽慁掍揮昬梡梱棔殙涽渾湣湷焄焝琿眃睧睯緄緍緡繉葷蔒觨諢轋閽顐餛餫鼲

huo
或活火伙货和获祸豁霍惑嚯镬耠劐藿攉锪蠖钬夥化扮灬瓠越佸俰剨吙咊咟嗀嚄嚿奯姡捇掝搉擭旤曤楇檴沎湱漷濊濩瀖焃獲癨眓矆矐礊禍秮秳穫篧耯腘膕臛艧萿蒦諕謋豰貨趏過邩鈥鍃鑊閄隻雘靃騞魊

i
乁

j

ji
几及急既即机鸡积记级极计挤己季寄纪系基激吉脊际汲肌嫉姬绩缉饥迹棘蓟技冀辑伎祭剂悸济籍寂期其奇忌齐妓继集给革击圾箕讥畸稽疾墼洎鲚屐齑戟鲫嵇矶稷戢虮诘笈暨笄剞叽蒺跻嵴掎跽霁唧畿荠瘠玑羁丌偈芨佶赍楫髻咭蕺觊麂骥殛岌亟犄乩芰哜倚卟厝居彐揖棋洁猗疵瘵睽瞿秸粢结脔萁蕲藉蜡觇觌讦郅隔骑丮乁亼伋偮僟兾刉刏剤劑勣卙卽叝吇呰喞嗘嘰嚌坖垍堲塉墍妀姞姼尐屰岋峜嵆嶯帺幾庴廭彑彶徛忣惎愱憿懠懻揤撃撠撽擊擠攲敧旡旣暩曁枅梞楖極槉槣樭機橶檕檝檵櫅櫭毄汥泲淁済湒漃漈潗濈濟瀱焏犱狤璂璣璾畟痵癠癪皀皍瞉磯禝禨稘稩穄穊積穖穧筓箿簊簎糭紀紒級結給継緝縘績繋繫繼罽羇羈耤耭胔脨膌臮艥艻芶苙茍茤莋萕葪蒩蔇蕀薊薺蘄蘎蘮蘻虀蝍螏蟣蟻蟿蠀裚褀襀襋覉覊覘覬覿觙觭計訐記誋諅諔譏譤谻谿賫賷趌趞跂跡踑踖踦蹐蹟躋躤躸輯轚郆鄿銈銡錤鍓鏶鐖鑇鑙際隮雞雦雧霵霽鞊鞿韲颳飢饑騎驥鬾魝魢魥鮆鯚鯯鯽鰶鰿鱀鱭鱾鳮鵋鶏鶺鷄鷑鸄鹡齊齌齍齎齏

jia
家加假价架甲佳夹嘉驾嫁枷荚颊钾稼茄贾铗葭迦戛浃镓痂恝岬跏嘏伽胛笳珈瘕郏袈蛱呷咖夏押拮挈挟揩暇袷铪颉骆骱傢價叚唊圿埉夓夾婽宊幏徦忦戞扴抸拁挾揳擖斚斝梜椵榎榢槚檟毠泇浹犌猰猳玾筴糘耞脥腵莢蛺蝦裌豭貑賈跲郟鉀鉫鉿鋏鎵頡頬頰餄饸駕駱鴶鵊麚

jian
见件减尖间键贱肩兼建检箭煎简剪歼监坚奸健艰荐剑渐溅涧鉴浅践捡柬笺俭碱硷拣舰槛缄茧饯翦鞯戋谏牮枧腱趼缣搛戬毽菅鲣笕谫楗囝蹇裥踺睑謇鹣蒹僭锏湔前喊堑孱柙滥犍箴纤茛谮钱险骞廴侟俴倹偂傔僣儉冿剣剱劍劎劒劔囏堅堿塹墹姦姧寋帴幵弿彅徤惤戔戩挸揀揃揵撿擶攕旔暕朁栫梘検椷椾榗樫橌橏橺檢檻櫼殱殲洊涀淺減湕漸澗濫濺瀐瀳瀸瀽熞熸牋猏玪珔瑊瑐監睷瞯瞷瞼碊磵礀礆礛稴筧箋篯簡籈籛糋絸緘縑繝繭纎纖聻臶艦艱菺葌葏葥蔪蕑蕳薦藆虃螹蠒袸襇襉襺見覵覸詃諓諫謭譖譼譾豜豣賎賤趝跈踐轞醎醶釰釼鈃銒銭鋄鋑鋻錢錬錽鍊鍳鍵鎫鏩鐗鐧鐱鑑鑒鑬鑯鑳钘閒間險靬鞬韀韉餞餰馢騫鬋鰎鰔鰜鰹鳒鳽鵳鶼鹸鹹鹻鹼麉黚黬

jiang
将讲江奖降浆僵姜酱蒋疆匠强桨虹豇礓缰犟耩绛茳糨洚红傋勥匞塂壃夅奨奬將嵹弜弶強彊摪摾杢槳橿櫤殭滰漿獎畕畺疅糡紅絳繮翞膙葁蔃蔣薑螀螿袶講謽醤醬韁顜鱂鳉

jiao
叫脚交角教较缴觉焦胶娇绞校搅骄狡浇矫郊嚼蕉轿窖椒礁饺铰酵侥剿徼艽僬蛟敫峤跤姣皎茭鹪噍醮佼湫鲛挢乔侨却咬妖学激纠菽纟僑僥儌劋勦勪卻呌喬嘂嘄嘐嘦噭嫶嬌嬓孂學峧嵺嶕嶠嶣恔悎憍憢憿挍捁摷撟撹攪敎敥敽敿斠晈暞曒樔橋櫵湬滘漖潐澆灂灚烄焳煍燋獥珓璬皦皭矯稾穚窌笅筊簥糾絞繳纐腳膠膲臫芁茮萩蕎藠虠蟜蟭覐覚覺訆譑譥賋趫趭踋蹻較轇轎鄗釂釥鉸鐎餃驕骹鮫鱎鵁鵤鷦鷮

jie
接节街借皆截解界结届姐揭戒介阶劫芥竭洁疥藉价楷秸桔杰捷诫睫家偈桀喈拮骱羯蚧嗟颉鲒婕碣讦孑疖诘亥假唧圾契她担拾暨概渴獬砝祖籍纥袷锴髫卩丯倢偼傑價刦刧刼劼卪吤唶啑嚌堦堺妎媎媘媫嫅尐屆岊岕崨嵑嵥嶰嶻巀幯庎徣忦悈扢掲搩擑擮擳斺昅曁桝椄楐楬楶榤構檞櫭毑洯渇湝滐潔煯犗狤玠琾畍疌痎癤砎礍稭節紇紒結絜繲耤脻艐莭菨蓵蛣蛶蜐蝍蝔蠘蠞蠽衱衸袓袺裓褯觧訐詰誡誱謯趌跲踕迼鉣鍇鍻階雃鞂鞊頡飷魝魪鮚鶛喼

jin
进近今仅紧金斤尽劲禁浸锦晋筋津谨巾襟烬靳廑瑾馑槿衿堇荩矜噤缙卺妗赆觐吟肋钅锓伒侭僅僸儘兓凚劤勁厪唫嚍埐堻墐壗婜嫤嬐嬧寖嶜巹惍慬搢斳晉枃榗歏殣浕溍漌濅濜煡燼珒琎琻瑨璡璶盡砛祲竻笒紟紾緊縉臸荕菫菳蓳藎覲觔訡謹賮贐進釒釿鋟錦饉馸鹶黅齽

jing
竟静井惊经镜京净敬精景警竞境径荆晶鲸粳颈兢茎睛劲痉靖肼獍阱腈弪刭憬婧胫菁儆旌迳靓泾晟檠氏烃箐蜻醒陉青丼亰仱俓倞傹儬凈剄劤勁坓坕坙妌婙婛宑巠幜弳徑憼擏旍暻曔桱梷橸殑汫汬浄涇淨濪瀞烴燝猄獷璄璟璥痙秔稉穽竧竫競竸粇経經聙脛荊莖葝蟼誩踁逕鋞鏡陘靑靘靚靜頚頴頸颕驚鯨鵛鶁鶄麖麠鼱

jiong
窘炯扃迥冂垧炅侰僒冋冏囧坰埛宭扄昋泂浻澃瀅烱煚煛熒熲燑燛絅綗臦臩蘏蘔褧逈銄鎣顈颎駉駫

jiu
就九酒旧久揪救纠舅究韭厩臼玖灸咎疚赳鹫蹴僦柩桕鬏鸠阄啾噍愁湫缪蝤丩乆乣倃剹勼匓匛匶奺廄廏廐慦捄揂揫摎朻杦柾樛橚殧氿汣湬牞畂稵穋窌糺糾紤繆舊舏萛镹韮鬮鯦鳩鷲麔齨

jou
欍

ju
句举巨局具距锯剧居聚拘菊矩沮拒惧鞠狙驹且据柜桔俱车咀疽踞炬倨醵裾屦犋苴窭飓锔椐苣琚掬榘龃趄莒雎遽橘踽榉鞫钜讵枸仇佝告姐娶拱渠瞿租篓菹蒌蘧蛆足邹鄹锄雏骄鬻伡侷俥倶僪冣凥劇勮匊圧坥埧埾壉姖娵婅婮寠屨岠岨崌巈弆忂怇怐怚愳懅懼抅拠挙挶捄揈揟據擧昛梮椇椈檋櫸欅歫毩毱泃泦洰涺淗湨澽焗焣爠犑狊珇痀眗砠秬窶筥簍簴籧粔粷罝耟聥腒臄舉艍萭葅蒟蒩蓻蔞蘜處虡蚷蜛螶袓襷詎諊豦貗趉趜趡跔跙跼踘蹫蹻躆躹軥輂邭郥郰郹鄒鉅鉏鋤鋦鋸鐻閰陱雛颶駏駒駶驕驧鮈鮍鮔鲏鴡鵙鵴鶋鶪鼰鼳齟車啹

juan
卷圈倦鹃捐娟眷绢鄄锩蠲镌狷桊涓隽擐泫甄眩睃蕊蜷身劵勌勬呟圏埍埢奆姢嶲巂帣弮悁惓慻捲朘梋棬淃焆獧瓹睊睠絭絹縳罥羂脧腃臇菤萒蔨蕋裐襈讂踡鋑鋗錈鎸鐫闂雋雟鞙韏飬餋鵍鵑

jue
决绝觉角爵掘诀撅倔抉攫嚼脚桷噱橛嗟觖劂爝矍镢獗珏崛蕨噘谲蹶孓厥乙屈柽狂穴蕞蛙蠼较阕阙鞒鳜亅傕刔勪匷叏吷啳埆壆夬妜孒屩屫崫嶡嶥弡彏憠憰戄挗捔撧斍橜欔欮殌氒決泬潏灍焆焳熦燋爑爴玃玦玨瑴璚疦瘚矞矡砄穱絕絶繑繘腳臄芵蕝虳蚗蟨蟩袦覐覚覺觼訣誳譎貜赽趉趹蹷蹻躩較逫鈌鐍鐝钁镼闋闕鞽駃騤骙髉鱖鴂鴃鶌鷢龣

jun
军君均菌俊峻龟竣骏钧浚郡筠麇皲捃匀旬狻訇隽儁勻呁埈姰寯懏攈晙桾汮濬焌焞燇珺畯皸皹碅箘箟莙葰蔨蚐蜠袀覠軍鈞銁銞鋆鍕陖雋餕馂駿鮶鲪鵔鵕鵘麏麕龜

k

ka
卡喀咯咖胩咔佧珈呿垰衉裃鉲

kai
开揩凯慨楷垲剀锎铠锴忾恺蒈劾喝核渴溘雉凱剴勓喫嘅噄塏奒嵦幆愒愷愾暟欬欯渇濭炌炏烗衉豈輆鍇鎎鎧鐦開闓闿颽

kan
看砍堪刊嵌坎槛勘龛戡侃瞰莰阚凵喊莶馅偘冚埳堿塪墈崁嵁惂扻栞檻欿歁監矙碪磡竷薟衎譼輡輱轁轗闞靬顑餡龕

kang
抗炕扛糠康慷亢钪闶伉坑奋杭沆荒匟囥嫝嵻忼摃槺漮犺砊穅粇躿邟鈧鏮閌阬骯鱇

kao
靠考烤拷栲犒尻铐彀挢搞槁丂嵪撟攷槀洘焅熇燺稾薧藳訄銬髛鮳鯌鲓

ke
咳可克棵科颗刻课客壳渴苛柯磕坷呵恪岢蝌缂蚵轲窠钶氪颏瞌锞稞珂髁疴嗑溘骒喀盍碣铪锕龛剋勀勊匼堁娔尅峇嵑嵙嶱悈愘愙揢搕敤榼樖欬歁殻毼渇濭炣牁犐痾砢硞碦磆礊礚窼簻緙翗胢艐萪薖衉袔課趷軻醘鈳鉿錁錒頦顆騍龕

kei
刻剋勀勊尅

ken
肯啃恳垦裉垠狠颀龈墾懇掯珢硍肎肻褃豤貇錹頎齦

keng
坑吭铿忐硎胫铒劥坈奟妔挳揁摼殸牼硁硍硜硻脛誙踁鉺銵鍞鏗阬

ki
怾

kong
空孔控恐倥崆箜穹腔埪宆悾椌涳矼硿羫躻錓鞚鵼

kou
口扣抠寇蔻芤眍筘叩佝妪挎冦剾劶嫗宼彄怐摳敂毆溝滱眗瞉瞘窛竘簆茠蔲釦鏂鷇

ku
哭库苦枯裤窟酷刳骷喾堀绔古圣挎掘跨俈嚳圐崫庫扝捁搰朏桍楛泏焅狜瘔矻硞秙窋絝胐袴褲趶跍郀鮬齁

kua
跨垮挎夸胯侉锞髁咵姱恗晇楇絓舿華蕐袔誇銙錁顝骻

kuai
快块筷会侩哙蒯浍郐狯脍傀蒉魁儈凷噲圦塊墤巜廥擓旝會澮獪璯糩膾蕢鄶駃鬠鱠鲙

kuan
宽款髋完棵颗寛寬梡欵歀窽窾鑧顆髖

kuang
矿筐狂框况旷匡眶诳邝纩夼诓圹贶哐兄枉湟磺逛丱儣劻匩卝壙岲廣忹恇懬懭抂昿曠況洭爌狅眖矌砿硄礦穬筺絋絖纊誆誑貺軖軠軦軭迋邼鄺鉱鋛鑛鵟黋

kui
亏愧奎窥葵魁馈盔傀岿匮愦揆睽跬聩篑喹逵暌蒉悝喟馗蝰隗夔缺臾觖踩阕顷溃刲匱卼嘳媿嬇尯巋巙憒戣晆楏楑樻櫆欳歸殨潰煃瞶磈窺簣籄聧聭聵胿腃膭蒍蕢藈蘬蘷虁虧謉蹞躨鄈鍨鍷鐀鑎闋闚頃頄頍頯顝餽饋騤骙

kun
捆困昆坤鲲锟髡琨醌阃悃卵混顽馄鳏龈堃堒壸壼婫尡崐崑晜梱涃潉焜熴猑瑻睏硱祵稇稛綑罤臗菎蜫裈裍裩褌豤貇錕閫閸頑餛騉髠髨鯤鰥鵾鶤鹍齦

kuo
阔扩廓适蛞栝会刳哙邝括噋噲懖拡挄擴會桰漷濶燭爥秳筈萿葀鄺闊霩鞟鞹韕頢髺鬠

l

la
拉啦辣蜡腊喇垃蓝落瘌邋砬剌旯摺癞儠嚹揦揧搚擸攋柆楋櫴溂爉瓎癩磖翋臈臘菈藞蝋蝲蠟辢鑞镴鞡鬎鯻鱲

lai
来赖莱濑赉崃涞铼籁徕睐黧癞來俫倈勑厲唻娕婡崍庲徠懶攋梾棶櫴淶瀨瀬猍琜癩睞筙箂籟萊藾襰誺賚賴逨郲釐錸頼顂騋鯠鵣鶆麳

lan
蓝兰烂拦篮懒栏揽缆滥阑谰婪澜览榄岚褴镧斓罱漤啉廪懔涟炼谏郴僋儖厱嚂囒坔壈壏嬾孄孏嵐幱廩惏懢懶擥攔攬斕暕欄欖欗浨湅漣濫瀾灆灠灡煉燗燣爁爛爤爦璼瓓礷籃籣糷繿纜葻藍蘫蘭襕襤襴襽覧覽諫譋讕躝醂鑭钄闌韊顲

lang
浪狼廊郎朗榔琅稂螂莨啷锒阆蒗羹踉俍勆哴唥埌塱嫏崀悢朖朤桹樃樠欴烺瑯硠筤羮脼艆蓈蓢蜋誏躴郒郞鋃鎯閬駺斏

lao
老捞牢劳烙涝落姥酪络佬潦耢铹醪铑唠栳崂痨僚撩獠蓼僗労勞咾哰嗠嘐嘮嫪嶗恅憥憦撈朥橑橯浶澇狫珯癆硓磱窂簩粩絡耮荖蛯蟧軂轑銠鐒顟髝鮱耂躼

le
了乐勒肋鳓仂叻泐嘞忇扐楽樂氻牞玏砳竻簕艻阞韷餎饹鰳

lei
类累泪雷垒勒擂蕾肋镭儡磊缧诔耒酹羸嫘檑嘞卢咧漯傫儽厽塁壘壨攂樏櫐櫑欙洡涙淚灅瓃畾瘣癗盧矋磥礌礧礨祱禷絫縲纇纍纝罍脷腂蔂蕌藟蘱蘲蘽虆蠝誄讄轠郲銇錑鐳鑘鑸靁頛頪類颣鱩鸓鼺

leng
冷棱楞愣塄倰堎睖碐稜薐踜輘

li
里离力立李例哩理利梨厘礼历丽吏砾漓莉傈荔俐痢狸粒沥隶栗璃鲤厉励犁黎篱郦鹂笠坜苈鳢缡跞蜊锂悝澧粝蓠枥蠡鬲呖砺嫠篥疠疬猁藜溧鲡戾栎唳醴轹詈骊罹逦俪喱雳黧莅俚蛎娌仂位列叻捩泣珞砬硌翮铄镉霾飒儮儷凓刕剓剺劙勵厤厯厲叓叕唎嚟嚦囄囇塛壢娳婯孋孷屴岦峛峲巁廲悡悧悷慄扐扚搮擽攊攦攭斄暦曆曞朸柂栃栛栵梸棃棙樆檪櫔櫟櫪欐欚歴歷氂沴沵浬涖淚濼濿瀝灑灕爄爏犂犛犡珕琍瑮瓅瓈瓑瓥癘癧皪盠盭睝矖砅磿礪礫礰禮禲秝穲竰筣籬粚粴糎糲綟縭纅纚脷艃苙茘荲菞蒚蒞蔾藶蘺蚸蛠蜧蝕蝷蟍蟸蠇蠣蠫裏裡褵觻謧讈豊貍赲躒轢轣邌邐酈醨釃釐鉝銐鋫鋰錅錑鎘鏫鑗鑠隷隸離靂靋颯驪鬁鬴鯉鯏鯬鱧鱱鱳鱺鳨鴗鵹鷅鸝麗麜

lia
俩倆

lian
连联练莲恋脸炼链敛怜廉帘镰涟蠊琏殓蔹鲢奁潋臁裢濂裣楝令娈挛搛瞵羸膦苓莶镧零亷僆劆匲匳嗹噒堜奩媡嫾嬚孌慩憐戀摙撿攣斂梿槏槤櫣欄歛殮浰湅溓漣澰濓瀲煉熑燫瑓璉磏稴簾籢籨練縺纞羷翴聨聫聮聯臉萰蓮薕薟蘝蘞螊褳襝覝謰譧蹥連鄻醶錬鍊鎌鏈鐮鬑鰊鰱鱄

liang
两亮辆凉粮梁量良晾谅俩粱墚靓踉椋魉莨惊蹒阆冫両俍倆倞兩哴唡啢喨悢掚樑涼湸煷簗糧綡緉脼蜋蜽裲諒蹣輌輛輬辌鍄閬靚駺魎

liao
了料撩聊撂疗廖燎辽僚寥镣潦钌蓼尥寮缭獠鹩嘹佬劳僇勞嫽尞尦屪嵺嶚嶛廫憀憭摎敹暸樛漻炓爎爒璙療瞭窷竂簝繚膋膫蟉蟟蟧豂賿蹘蹽轑遼鄝釕鏐鐐镠镽飂飉髎鷯藔

lie
列裂猎劣烈咧埒捩鬣趔躐冽洌例栗膊邋倈儠劦劽哷埓奊姴峢巁巤忚挒挘擸棙櫑毟浖烮煭燤爄爉犣猟獵睙綟聗脟臘茢蛚迾颲鬛鮤鱲鴷

lin
林临淋邻磷鳞赁吝拎琳霖凛遴嶙蔺粼麟躏辚廪懔瞵檩膦啉任渗阴亃伈僯凜厸壣崊廩恡悋惏懍撛斴晽暽橉檁涁滲潾澟瀶焛燐獜玪璘甐疄痳癛癝碄稟箖粦繗翷臨菻藺賃蹸躙躪轔轥鄰鏻閵隣顲驎魿鱗麐

ling
另令领零铃玲灵岭龄凌陵菱伶羚棱翎蛉苓绫瓴酃呤泠棂柃鲮聆囹冷怜拎磷钉倰刢坽夌姈婈孁岺崚嶺彾掕昤朎櫺欞淩澪瀮炩燯爧狑琌皊砱祾秢竛笭紷綾舲蓤蔆蕶蘦衑袊裬詅跉軨輘醽釘鈴錂閝阾霊霗霛霝靇靈領駖魿鯪鴒鸰鹷麢齡齢龗

liu
六流留刘柳溜硫瘤榴琉馏碌陆绺锍鎏镏浏骝旒鹨熘遛偻抡泖泵游聊蒌蓼铆僂劉嚠塯媹嬼嵧廇懰斿旈栁桞桺橊橮沠漻澑瀏熮珋瑠瑬璢畂畄畱疁癅磂磟綹罶羀翏膢蒥蓅蔞藰蟉裗蹓鉚鋶鎦鏐鐂镠陸雡霤飀飂飅飗餾駠駵騮驑鬸鰡鶹鷚鹠麍

lo
咯囖

long
龙拢笼聋隆垄弄咙窿陇垅胧珑茏泷栊癃砻宠庞总儱厐哢嚨壟壠寵屸嶐巃巄徿攏昽曨朧梇槞櫳湰滝漋瀧爖瓏眬矓硦礱礲竉竜篢篭籠聾蕯蘢蝕蠪蠬衖襱谾豅贚躘鏧鑨隴霳靇驡鸗龍龐龒龓

lou
楼搂漏陋露娄篓偻蝼镂蒌耧髅喽瘘嵝牢僂嘍塿婁寠屚嶁廔慺摟樓溇漊熡甊瘺瘻瞜窶簍耬膢艛蔞螻謱軁遱鏤鞻髏

lu
路露录鹿陆炉卢鲁卤芦颅庐碌掳绿虏赂戮潞禄麓六鲈栌渌蓼逯泸轳氇簏橹辂垆胪噜镥辘漉撸璐鸬鹭舻捋摅滤瘳肤角谷酪侓僇剹勎勠嗠嚕嚧圥坴塶塷壚娽峍廘廬彔挔捛摝擄擼攄攎枦椂樐樚櫓櫨氌淕淥滷漊澛濾瀂瀘熝爐獹玈琭璷瓐甪盝盧睩矑硉硵磠祿稑穋箓簬簵簶籙籚粶緑纑罏翏膔膚膟臚舮艣艪艫菉蓾蔍蕗蘆虂虜螰蠦觮觻賂趢踛蹗輅轆轤鄜醁鈩錄録錴鏀鏕鏴鐪鑥鑪陸顱騄騼髗魯魲鯥鱳鱸鴼鵦鵱鷺鸕鹵黸

luan
乱卵滦峦孪挛栾銮脔娈鸾乿亂圝圞奱孌孿巒攣曫欒灓灤癴癵羉脟臠臡薍虊覶釠鑾鵉鸞

lve
略掠锊率药剠圙寽擽畧稤藥詻鋝鋢

lun
论轮抡伦沦仑纶囵侖倫圇埨婨崘崙惀掄棆淪溣睔碖磮稐綸耣腀菕蜦論踚輪錀陯鯩

luo
落罗锣裸骡烙箩螺萝洛骆逻络咯荦漯蠃雒倮硌椤捋脶瘰摞泺珞镙猡乐果格橐烁猓碌蜾蠡袼跞路铬儸儽剆啰囉峈挼捰攎攞攭曪樂櫟欏欙濼爍犖玀癳皪砢硦礫笿籮絡纙羅腡臝茖蓏蘿蛒蝸覶覼詻躒躶邏鉻鎯鏍鑼頱饠駱騾驘鮥鱳鵅鸁洜

lv
绿率铝驴旅屡滤吕律氯缕侣虑履偻膂榈闾捋褛稆卢娄庐篓累蒌镂鲁鹿侶儢勴卛呂哷垏壘婁寠寽屢嵂廬慮慺曥梠樓櫖櫚櫨氀焒爈瘻盧瞜祣穞穭箻簍絽綠緑縷繂膐膢葎蔞藘褸謱軁郘鋁録鏤鑢閭馿驢魯鷜

m
呒呣嘸

ma
吗妈马嘛麻骂抹码玛蚂摩唛蟆犸嬷杩么呐蓦貉貊靡麽亇傌嗎嘜媽嫲嬤孖尛榪溤犘獁瑪痲睰碼礣祃禡罵蔴螞蟇遤鎷閁馬駡驀鬕鰢鷌麼

mai
买卖迈埋麦脉劢霾荬咪哩派唛佅勱嘪売脈蕒薶衇貍買賣邁霡霢鷶麥

man
满慢瞒漫蛮蔓曼馒埋谩幔鳗墁螨镘颟鞔缦熳幕蹒僈姏嫚屘悗慲摱槾樠満滿澫澷獌睌瞞矕絻縵蔄蘰蟃蟎蠻襔謾蹣鄤鏋鏝顢饅鬗鬘鰻

mang
忙芒盲莽茫氓硭邙蟒漭朦瞢龙厖吂哤壾娏尨庬恾朚杗杧汒浝牤牻狵甿痝盳硥笀茻莾蘉蛖蠎釯鋩铓駹鸏鹲龍龒

mao
毛冒帽猫矛卯貌茂贸铆锚茅耄茆瑁蝥髦懋昴牦瞀峁袤蟊旄泖侔勖描牟耗蛑冃冇冐務堥夘媢嵍愗戼暓枆楙毣毷氂渵犛獏皃眊秏笷緢罞芼萺蓩蝐覒貇貓貿軞鄚鄮酕鉚鉾錨霿髳鶜

me
么麽嚒嚜嚰孭庅濹癦麼

mei
没每煤镁美酶妹枚霉玫眉梅寐昧媒糜媚谜沫嵋猸袂湄浼鹛莓魅镅楣味坶墨某凂呅嚜坆堳塺媄媺嬍嵄徾抺挴攗攟栂楳槑櫗毎氼沒沬渼湈溦煝燘珻瑂痗眊眛睂睸矀祙禖篃羙脄脢腜膴苺葿蘪蝞跊躾郿鋂鎂鎇韎鬽鶥黣黴

men
门们闷懑扪钔焖汶满玟鞔亹們怋悗悶惛懣捫暪椚殙満滿燜玣玧璊瞞穈菛虋鍆門閅

meng
猛梦蒙锰孟盟檬萌氓礞蜢勐懵甍蠓虻朦艋艨瞢明瞑蟊蟒黾儚冡夢夣嫇尨幪庬懜懞掹擝曚橗氋溕濛獴瓾甿矇矒罞莔萠蕄蝱鄳鄸鋂錳雺霚霥霧霿靀顭饛髳鯍鯭鱦鸏鹲黽鼆

mi
米密迷眯蜜谜觅秘弥幂靡糜泌醚蘼縻咪汨麋祢猕弭谧芈脒宓敉嘧糸冖尔幺摩溟獯辟侎冞冪劘哋塓孊宻尒尓峚幎幦彌戂摵擟擵攠榓樒檷櫁沕沵洣淧渳滵漞濔濗瀰灖熐爢爾獼瓕眫眽瞇瞴祕禰穈簚籋粎罙羃羋苾葞蒾蓂蔝蔤藌蝆袮覓覔覛詸謎謐醾醿釄銤鑖镾鸍麊麛鼏

mian
面棉免绵眠缅勉冕娩腼湎眄沔黾渑冥泯瞑缗宀丏俛偭勔厸喕婂媔嬵愐檰櫋汅湣澠牑矈矊矏糆絻綿緍緜緡緬臱芇莬葂蝒蠠靣靦鮸麪麫麵麺黽

miao
秒苗庙妙描瞄藐渺眇缪缈淼喵杪鹋邈吵猫纱蜱仯媌嫹庿廟彯玅竗篎紗緢緲訬鱙鶓

mie
灭蔑咩篾蠛乜咪谂吀哶孭幭懱搣櫗滅瀎眜薎衊覕鑖鱴鴓旀

min
民抿敏闽皿悯珉愍缗闵玟苠泯黾鳘岷汶眠绳僶冧冺刡勄呡垊姄崏忞怋慜憫捪敃敯旻旼暋渂湏湣潣琘琝瑉痻盷盿砇碈笢笽簢緍緡繩罠蠠賯鈱錉鍲閔閩鰵鴖黽

ming
名明命鸣铭螟盟冥瞑暝茗溟酩萌佲凕姳嫇慏掵朙榠洺猽眀眳蓂覭詺鄍銘鳴

miu
谬缪繆謬

mo
摸磨抹末膜墨没莫默魔模摩摹漠陌蘑脉沫万无冒寞秣瘼殁镆嫫谟蓦貊貘麽茉馍耱么伯佰勿帕抚昧百藐蟆袜貉貌嘿嬷劘劰嗼嚤嚩圽塻妺嫼尛帓帞怽懡戂撫擵攠昩暯枺橅歾歿沒瀎無爅狢皌眜眽眿瞐瞙砞礳粖糢絈絔縸纆艒莈藦蛨蟔袹謨謩譕貃貈銆鏌靺鞨饃饝驀髍魩魹麼麿黙

mou
某谋牟眸蛑鍪侔缪哞件厶婺毋袤蝥劺呣堥恈敄桙洠瞴繆蟱謀鉾鞪鴾麰踎

mu
木母亩幕目墓牧牟模穆暮牡拇募慕睦姆姥钼毪坶沐仫苜婺缪呒嘿凩墲娒峔幙慔朷楘樢毣氁炑牳狇獏畆畒畝畞畮砪縸繆胟艒茻莯萺蚞踇鉧鉬雮霂鞪

n
嗯哏咹

na
那拿哪纳钠娜呐南衲捺镎肭内呶箬絮乸內吶嗱妠抐拏挐淰秅笚笝篛納蒘蒳袦訤詉誽豽貀蹃軜郍鈉鎿雫靹魶

nai
乃耐奶奈氖哪萘艿柰鼐佴能倷妳嬭孻廼掜搱摨渿熋疓耏腉螚褦迺釢錼

nan
难南男赧囡蝻楠喃腩囝摊滩颌侽妠娚婻嫨弇戁抩揇攤暔枏枬柟湳灘煵畘莮萳諵遖難

nang
囊馕曩囔攮哝乪儾噥嚢崀憹搑擃欜涳瀼灢蘘蠰譨饢鬞齉

nao
闹脑恼挠淖孬铙瑙垴呶蛲猱硇浇匘堖夒婥嫐峱嶩巎巙怓悩惱憹撓橈檂澆獶獿碙碯脳腝腦臑蝚蟯詉譊鐃閙鬧

ne
呢哪那呐讷疔疒吶抐眲訥

nei
内哪馁那內娞婑氝浽脮腇錗餒餧鮾鯘

nen
嫩恁枘媆嫰腝臑

neng
能而耐竜螚

ni
你泥拟腻逆呢溺倪尼匿妮霓铌昵坭祢猊伲怩鲵睨旎嶷慝滠伱儗儞児兒埿堄妳婗嫟嬭嬺孨孴屔屰彌惄愵懝抐抳掜擬晲暱柅棿檷氼淣濔濘瀰灄狔痆眤禰秜籾縌聻胒腝膩臡苨薿蚭蛪蜺袮觬誽譺貎跜輗迡郳鈮鉨鑈镾隬馜鯢麑齯聣

nian
年念捻撵拈碾蔫粘廿黏辇鲇鲶埝趁辗卄哖唸姩捵撚攆榐涊淰溓痆秊秥簐艌趂跈蹍蹨躎輦輾鮎鯰鵇

niang
娘酿嬢孃醸釀

niao
鸟尿袅茑脲嬲尥溺嫋嬝尦樢茮蔦裊褭鳥

nie
捏镍聂孽涅镊啮陧蘖嗫臬蹑颞乜倪囡埝幸捻摄肀喦噛嚙囁囐囓圼孼峊嵒嵲嶭巕帇惗掜揑摂摰攝敜枿棿槷櫱痆篞籋糱糵聶臲苶菍蠥褹諗讘踂踗踙躡鉨鉩銸鋷錜鎳鑈鑷钀闑隉顳齧

nin
您恁囜拰脌

ning
拧凝宁柠狞泞佞甯咛聍冰年攘疑侫儜嚀嬣寍寕寗寜寧擰橣檸澝濘獰矃聹苧薴鑏鬡鬤鸋

niu
牛扭纽钮拗妞狃忸蚴怓抝杻汼沑炄牜紐莥鈕靵

nong
弄浓农脓哝侬咔廾儂噥憹挊挵欁濃癑禯秾穠繷膿莀蕽襛農辳醲齈燶

nou
耨啂嬬搙擩槈檽獳羺譨譳鎒鐞

nu
怒努奴孥胬驽弩仅呶帑褥伖伮傉搙擩砮笯詉駑

nuan
暖濡奻渜湪煖煗餪

nue
虐疟谑硸

nun
黁

nuo
挪诺懦糯娜喏傩锘搦呐哪掉那难需儺吶堧媠嫷愞懧掿搙搻梛榒橠毭渪稬穤糑糥耎袲袳諾蹃逽郍鍩難

nv
女衄钕恧狃絮肭朒沑籹聏衂釹

nve
疟虐婩瘧

o
哦喔噢筽

ou
偶呕欧藕鸥区沤殴怄瓯讴耦抠握渥纡遇區吘吽嘔塸慪摳敺櫙歐毆漚澫熰甌紆腢膒蓲蕅藲謳醧鏂鴎鷗齵

p

pa
怕爬趴啪耙扒帕琶派筢杷葩叭吧把芭钯妑帊掱汃潖皅舥苩袙跁鈀

pai
派排拍牌迫徘湃哌俳蒎啡脾棑椑犤猅箄簰腗輫鎃

pan
盘盼判攀畔潘叛磐番般胖襻蟠袢泮拚爿蹒伴半卞姗审弁彦扳拌片皤繁鄱乑冸坢姍媻宷審幋搫柈槃沜洀湴溿瀊瀋炍牉牓畨盤盻眅眫碆磻籓縏膰蒰螌褩詊跘踫蹣鋬鎜鑻闆鞶頖鵥

pang
旁胖耪庞乓膀磅滂彷逄螃仿傍彭房方蒡逢镑厐嗙夆嫎尨徬汸沗炐篣肨胮膖舽蠭覫趽鎊雱霶髈鰟鳑龎龐

pao
跑抛炮泡刨袍咆狍匏庖疱脬包抱胞苞飑鲍嚗垉奅拋摽炰爮犥瓟皰砲礟礮穮窌脟萢藨蚫袌褜謈軳鉋铇鞄颮鮑麃麅麭

pei
陪配赔呸胚佩培沛裴旆锫帔醅霈辔倍啡坏妃掊淠艴茇蜚伂俖垺妚姵婄媐嶏怌抷攈斾昢柸棑毰浿犻珮琣琲笩肧茷蓜衃裵賠轡錇阫陫馷駍

pen
喷盆湓吩本汾呠喯噴歕濆瓫翉翸葐衯

peng
碰捧棚砰蓬朋彭鹏烹硼膨抨澎篷怦堋蟛嘭亨傍庄旁滂苹迸逢倗傰剻匉塜塳弸恲憉挷掽搒摓梈椖椪槰樥泙淎淜漨漰熢痭皏硑磞稝竼篣絣纄胓芃荓莑蟚踫軯軿輣輧逬錋鑝閛韸韼駍騯髼鬅鬔鵬

pi
批皮披匹劈辟坯屁脾僻疲痞霹琵毗啤譬砒否貔丕圮媲癖仳擗郫甓枇睥蜱鼙邳吡陂铍庀罴埤纰陴淠噼蚍裨俾副卑坏培帔庇庳扑拂比濞疋痦篦芘苤萆蕃蚌被鄱钚颇伓伾噽嚊嚭壀妚嫓岯崥嶏怶悂憵抷揊旇朇枈椑榌毘毞渒潎澼炋焷狉狓猈疈痺睤磇礔礕秛秠稫笓箆篺簲粃紕罷羆翍耚肶脴腗膍苉蚽蚾螕螷蠯諀豼豾釽鈈鈚鈲鈹鉟銔銢錃錍鎞闢阰隦鞞頗顖駓髬魮魾鮍鲏鴄鵧鷿鸊

pian
片篇骗偏便扁翩缏犏骈胼蹁谝平蝙褊辩囨媥徧楄楩猵璸緶腁萹覑諚諞貵賆跰辯駢騈騗騙骿魸鶣

piao
票飘漂瓢朴螵莩嫖瞟殍缥嘌骠剽膘髟僄勡彯徱慓摽旚潎犥皫磦篻縹翲蔈薸謤醥闝顠飃飄驃驫骉魒

pie
瞥撇氕苤丿肺蔽嫳撆暼潎覕鐅

pin
品贫聘拼频嫔榀姘牝颦匕娉拚泵嚬嬪朩汖玭琕矉砏礗穦薲蘋貧頻顰馪驞

ping
平凭瓶评屏乒萍苹坪冯娉鲆枰俜砰冖秤倗凴呯塀娦屛岼帡帲幈慿憑檘泙洴涄淜焩玶甁甹砯硑竮箳簈缾聠胓艵荓蓱蘋蚲蛢評軿輧郱鉼頩馮鮃

po
破坡颇婆泼迫泊魄朴繁粕笸皤钋陂鄱攴叵珀钷溥膊跛霸泺哱嘙奤娝尀尃屰岥岶巿廹搫敀昢桲椺櫇洦淿湐溌潑濼烞猼皛砶翍蒪蔢謈酦醱釙鉕鏺頗馞駊髆

pou
剖掊裒培抱涪褒踣部锫吥咅哣垺堷婄抔抙捊棓犃箁裦襃郶錇颒

pu
扑铺谱脯仆蒲葡朴菩莆瀑埔圃浦堡普暴镨噗匍溥濮氆蹼璞镤剥卜扶攴甫苻攵曝僕剝圑圤墣巬巭抪捗撲擈暜柨樸檏潽炇烳獛痡瞨砲秿穙箁纀舖舗荹菐蒱蜅襆襥諩譜豧贌酺鋪鏷鐠陠駇鯆鵏

q

qi
起其七气期齐器妻骑汽棋奇欺漆启戚柒岂砌弃泣祁凄企乞契歧祈栖畦脐崎稽迄缉沏讫旗祺颀骐屺岐蹊萁蕲桤憩芪荠萋芑汔亟鳍俟槭嘁蛴綦亓欹琪麒琦蜞圻杞葺碛淇祗耆绮丌伎偈切刺勤吃吱宿己忮忾恝技抵挈揭支枝济渍甭畸示綮趿逗亝倛傶僛剘呇呮咠唘唭啓啔啟喰噐埼夡娸婍岓嵜帺忔忯恓悽愒愭愾慼慽憇懠扢扱扺拞捿掑摖攲敧斉斊旂晵暣朞栔桼梩棄棊棨棲榿檱櫀欫毄気氣洓淒済渏湆湇滊漬濝濟炁焏猉玂玘璂甈疧盀盵矵碁碕碶磎磜磧磩礘祇禥禨稘竒簯簱籏粸紪絜綥綨綺緀緕緝纃缼罊肐肵臍舙艩芞萕薺藄蘄蚑蚔蚚蜝螇螧蟣蟿蠐衹袳裿褀褄觭訖諆諬諿豈趞跂踑踖踦躤躩軙軝迉邔郪鄿釮錡鏚鐖锜闙隑霋頎饑騎騏騹鬐鬾鬿魌魕鮨鯕鰭鲯鵸鶀鶈麡鼜齊齮

qia
恰卡掐洽髂袷葜咭客挈疴鲒佉價冾圶帢愘抲拤揢搳擖楬殎矻硈磍絜跒酠鞐鮚

qian
前钱千牵浅签欠铅嵌钎迁钳乾谴谦潜歉纤扦遣黔堑仟岍钤褰箝掮搴倩慊悭愆虔芡荨缱佥芊阡肷茜椠犍骞凄凵寨忏撖柑涔渐湔筋羟腱赶锓鹣龈乹仱伣俔偂傔僉儙刋厱唊嗛圱圲塹墘壍奷婜媊嬱孅孯岒嵰廞忴悓慳扲拑拪挳掔揃揵摼撁撍攐攑攓朁杄杴棈榩槏槧橬檶櫏欦欿歁歬汘汧淒淺漸潛濳濽灊灒炶煔熑燂燫牽皘竏箞篏篟簽籖籤粁綪縴繾羥羬脥膁臤艌苂茾荕葥葴蒨蔳蕁藖蚈蚙蜸諐謙譴谸軡輤遷釺鈆鈐鉆鉗鉛銭鋟錎錢鍼鎆鏲鐱鑓鑯開雃靬韆顅馯騚騝騫鬜鬝鰜鰬鳒鳽鵮鶼鹐黚齦

qiang
强枪墙抢腔呛羌蔷将蜣跄戗襁戕炝镪锖锵羟樯嫱哐庆控爿箐跫創勥唴啌嗆嗴墏墻嬙將嶈廧強彊慶戧搶摤摪斨椌槍檣殻溬漒熗牄牆猐獇玱琷瑲矼篬繈繦羗羥羫羻艢蔃薔蘠親謒蹌蹡錆鎗鏘鏹顩鶬鸧

qiao
桥瞧敲巧翘锹壳鞘撬悄俏窍雀乔侨峭橇樵荞跷硗憔谯鞒愀缲诮劁削峤愁招捎搞敫校毳焦硝茭蕉跤醮铫骄偢僑僺勪喬喿嘺噭塙墝墧墽嫶嵪嶠帩幓幧摮撽槗橋橾殼毃潐焳燆燋犞癄睄硚碻磝磽礄礉窯竅箾繑繰翹荍菬蕎藮蟜誚譑譙趫趬踃踍蹺蹻躈郻鄗鄡鄥釥銚鍫鍬鏒鐈鐰陗鞩鞽韒頝顤顦驕骹髚髜

qie
切且怯窃茄砌郄趄惬锲妾箧慊伽挈唼喋契婕捷沏漆脞蕺鲽倢倿偼匧厒媫帹悏愜朅椄洯淁疌癿稧穕竊笡篋籡緁聺苆藒蛣蛪詧跙踥鍥鐑魥鯜鰈

qin
亲琴侵勤擒寝秦芹沁禽钦吣覃矜衾芩溱廑嗪螓噙揿檎锓堇槿浸渗蓁蕲衿颌儭厪吢唚坅埁埐墐媇嫀寑寢寴嵚嶔嶜庈廞忴慬懃懄扲抋捦搇撳斳昑梫橬櫬欽涁滲澿濅瀙珡琹瘽矝笉綅耹肣臤菣菦菳藽蘄蚙螼蠄親誛赺赾鈂鈊鈙鋟雂靲頜顉顩駸骎鬵鮼鳹

qing
请轻清青情晴氢倾庆擎顷亲卿氰圊謦檠箐苘蜻黥罄鲭磬綮倩声精胜傾儬凊剠勍啨埥夝媇寈庼廎慶掅擏暒棾樈檾櫦殑殸氫涇淸渹漀濪玪甠硘硜碃綪莔葝請軽輕郬鑋靑靘頃鯖鶄

qiong
穷琼跫穹邛蛩茕銎筇鞠儝卭嬛宆惸憌桏橩焪焭煢熍琁璚瓊瓗睘瞏窮竆笻舼藑藭蛬赹

qiu
求球秋丘泅仇邱囚酋龟楸蚯裘糗蝤巯逑俅虬赇鳅犰湫鼽遒区团宿惆愀氽艽邺钆馗鸠丠厹叴唒坵媝寈崷巰恘扏捄搝朹梂櫹殏毬氿汓浗渞湬湭煪牫玌璆皳盚秌穐篍紌絿緧肍莍萩蓲蘒虯蛷蝵蟗蠤觓觩訄訅賕趜趥逎醔釓釚釻銶鞦鞧鮂鯄鰌鰍鰽鱃鳩鵭鶖鹙龜龝

qu
去取区娶渠曲趋趣屈驱蛆躯龋戌蠼蘧祛蕖磲劬诎鸲阒麴癯衢黢璩氍觑蛐朐瞿岖苣句巨组蜡遽鞠鞫驺匚伹佉佢刞匤匷區厺呿坥岨岴嶇弆忂怚憈戵抾敺斪欋欪毆浀淭灈焌璖竘竬筁籧粬紶組絇翑翵耝胊胠脥臞菃葋蚼蝺螶蟝蠷衐袪覰覷覻詓詘誇誳趍趜趨跔跙跼躣軀軥迲郥鉤鐻鑺閴闃阹駆駈騶驅髷魼鮈鰸鱋鴝鶌鸜麮麯麹鼁鼩齲

quan
全权劝圈拳犬泉券颧痊醛铨筌绻诠辁畎鬈悛蜷荃卷圳拴桊獾纯鹳犭佺勧勸啳圏埢姾婘孉峑巏巻弮恮惓捲搼栒棬椦楾槫権權汱洤湶灥烇牶牷犈琯瑔甽矔硂純絟綣縓腃葲虇蠸觠詮謜譔跧踡輇酄銓鐉闎韏顴駩騡鰁鳈鸛齤

que
却缺确雀瘸鹊炔榷阙阕悫决屈攉猎舄芍鸟傕卻埆塙墧崅愨慤搉敠殻毃汋決燩獡皵硞碏確碻礐礭舃蒛蚗趞踖躤闋闕隺鳥鵲

qun
群裙麇逡遁囷夋宭峮帬歏箘羣裠踆輑麏麕

r

ra
亽罖

ran
染燃然冉髯苒蚺冄卪呥嘫姌媣柟橪熯珃繎肰舑蒅蚦衻袇袡蹨髥

rang
让嚷瓤攘壤穰禳镶儴勷壌孃忀懹欀瀼爙獽穣纕蘘蠰譲讓躟鑲鬤

rao
饶绕扰荛桡娆挠缭嬈撓擾橈犪穘繚繞蕘蟯襓遶隢饒

re
热若惹喏偌捼渃熱蹃

ren
人任忍认刃仁韧妊纫壬饪轫仞荏葚衽稔儿恁亻仭刄姙屻忈忎扨朲杒栠栣梕棯涊牣秂秹紉紝絍綛纴肕腍芢荵菍袵訒認讱躵軔釰鈓銋靭靱韌飪餁魜鵀祍

reng
仍扔戎穰耳艿礽芿辸陾

ri
日囸氜釰鈤馹驲

rong
容绒融溶熔荣戎蓉冗茸榕狨嵘肜蝾缛隔颂傇傛坈媶嫆嬫宂峵嵤嶸巆搈搑摉曧栄榮榵毧氄瀜烿爃瑢穁穃絨縙縟羢茙螎蠑褣軵鎔镕頌駥髶

rou
肉揉柔糅蹂鞣厹媃宍楺渘煣瑈瓇禸粈腬莥葇蝚輮鍒鑐韖騥髳鰇鶔

ru
如入汝儒茹乳褥辱蠕孺蓐襦铷嚅缛濡薷颥溽洳女月肉需侞偄吺咮嗕媷嬬嶿帤扖挐擩曘杁桇檽渪燸獳筎縟繻肗臑蒘蕠袽込邚鄏醹銣鑐顬鱬鳰鴑鴽

rua
挼

ruan
软阮朊濡需偄堧壖媆嫰愞撋檽渪燸瑌瓀碝礝緛耎腝蝡軟輭

rui
瑞蕊锐睿芮蚋枘蕤兑内绥钠兊兌內叡壡婑惢抐撋桵棁橤汭甤笍綏緌繠苼蕋蘂蘃蜹踒鈉銳鋭鏸

run
润闰撋橍潤閏閠

ruo
若弱箬偌惹溺芮叒婼嵶挼捼撋楉渃焫爇篛蒻鄀鰙鰯鶸

s

sa
撒洒萨挲仨卅飒脎檫蔡摋攃桬櫒殺泧潵灑纚蕯薩訯躠鈒鎝鏾钑隡霅靸鞈颯馺

sai
塞腮鳃思赛噻僿嗮嘥愢揌毢毸簑簺賽顋鰓

san
三散伞叁馓糁毵霰参彡氵俕傘傪厁參叄叅壭帴弎橵毶毿潵犙糂糝糣糤繖蔘謲鏒鏾閐饊鬖

sang
桑丧嗓颡磉搡喪桒槡纕褬鎟顙

sao
扫嫂搔骚梢埽鳋臊缫瘙哨燥缲慅懆掃掻橾氉溞煰矂縿繅繰鄵鐰颾騒騷髞鯵鰠鰺鱢鲹

se
色涩瑟塞啬铯穑寨槭泣渍蔷铋铩嗇廧愬懎拺擌栜歮歰洓渋溹漬澀澁濇濏瀒琗璱瘷穡穯粣繬薔虩譅轖鉍銫鎍鎩鏼闟雭飋閪

sei
涁聓

sen
森掺渗摻槮滲篸襂

seng
僧鬙

sh

sha
杀沙啥纱傻砂刹莎厦煞杉嗄唼鲨霎铩痧裟挲歃噎接摄赊乷倽儍剎唦啑喢帹廈挱摂摋攝榝樧殺濈猀硰箑粆紗繌繺翜翣菨萐蔱賒賖鎩閯閷霅魦鯊鯋

shai
晒筛色酾摋攦曬殺篩簁簛籭繺術諰閷

shan
山闪衫善扇杉删煽单珊掺赡栅苫掸膳陕汕擅缮嬗蟮芟禅跚鄯潸鳝姗剡骟疝膻讪钐舢埏儋搀檀澹邓颤彡凵髟傓僐僤儃刪剼単單嘇圸墠墡壇姍嶦幓挻掞搧摻擔攙敾晱曏曑杣柵椫樿檆櫼潬澘灗炶烻煔熌狦猭痁睒磰禪穇笘笧縿繕纔羴羶脠葠蔪蟬蟺襂襳覢訕謆譱贍赸軕邖釤銏鐥閃閄閊陝顃顫饍騸鯅鱓鱔鱣鳣歚

shang
上伤尚商赏晌墒汤裳熵觞绱殇垧场丄仩傷埫場塲尙恦愓慯扄殤湯滳漡禓緔蔏螪蠰觴謪賞踼鑜鞝鬺贘

shao
少烧捎哨勺梢稍邵韶绍芍召鞘苕劭潲艄蛸筲削招搜溲笤绡杓佋卲娋弰旓柖焼燒燿玿睄紹綃綤莦萔萷蕱袑輎鞩韒颵髾鮹

she
社射蛇设舌摄舍折涉赊赦慑奢歙厍畲猞麝滠佘拾揲睫碟聂蛞厙奓弽慴懾抴挕捨摂摵攝檨欇涻渉灄畬磼聶舎葉蔎虵蛥蠂設賒賖輋闍阇鞨韘騇

shei
谁

shen
身伸深婶神甚渗肾审申沈绅呻参砷什娠慎葚糁莘诜谂矧椹渖蜃哂胂信吲抻震伔侁侺兟參叄叅嘇堔妽姺嫀嬸孞宷審屾峷幓弞愼扟抌搷昚曋柛棯椮榊槮氠涁淰滲瀋燊珅甡甧瘆瘮眒眘瞋瞫矤祳穼籶籸紳綝罙罧脤腎葠蓡蔘薓蜄裑覾訠訷詵諗讅谉邥鉮鋠頣駪魫鯅鯓鯵鰰鰺鲹鵢黮

sheng
声省剩生升绳胜盛圣甥牲乘晟渑眚笙嵊丞冼垩姓媵甸乗偗剰勝呏墭娍憴斘昇晠曻枡榺橳殅殸泩渻湦澠焺狌珄琞竔箵縄繩聖聲苼蕂譝貹賸鉎鍟阩陞陹鱦鵿鼪

shi
是使十时事室市石师试史式识虱矢拾屎驶始似嘘示士世柿匙拭誓逝势什殖峙嗜噬失适仕侍释饰氏狮食恃蚀视实施湿诗尸豕莳埘铈舐鲥鲺贳轼蓍筮炻谥弑酾螫唑堤寺彖提斯汁液礻筛绎耆肢舍赫郝铊铩饣饬丗乨亊佀佦兘冟勢卋厔叓呞呩咶啇噓埶塒奭姼媞嬕実宩宲寔實屍峕崼嵵師弒徥忕忯恀惿戺揓旹昰時枾柹栻楴榁榯檡沶洂浉湜湤溡溮溼澤澨濕烒煶狧狶獅瑡畤痑眂眎眡睗祏禵秲竍笶笹箷篒篩簭籂籭絁繹胑舓葹蒒蒔蝕蝨褆褷襫襹視觢訑試詩諟諡謚識貰跩軾辻遈遞適遰遾邿醳釃釈釋釶鈰鉂鉃鉇鉈鉐鉽銴鍉鍦鎩飠飭飾餙餝馶駛魳鮖鯴鰘鰣鰤鳲鳾鶳鸤鼫鼭齛齥

shou
手受收首守瘦授兽售熟寿艏狩绶扌涛収嘼垨壽夀掱敊涭濤獣獸痩綬膄醻鏉

shu
书树数熟输梳叔属束术述蜀黍鼠淑赎孰蔬疏戍竖墅庶薯漱恕枢暑殊抒曙署舒姝摅秫纾沭毹腧塾菽殳澍倏俞售嗽娶揄朱杼涑疋荼薮豫透野镯除鹬忄丨侸俆俶倐儵兪咰婌孎尌尗屬庻忬怷悆捈捒掓攄數暏書朮杸柕樞樹橾毺氀潄潏潻濖瀭焂瑹璹疎癙稌竪籔糬紓紵絉綀翛荗蒁蒣薥藪藷虪蠴蠾術裋襡襩謶豎贖跾踈軗輸鄃鉥錰鏣鐲陎隃鮛鱪鱰鵨鶐鷸鸀鼡

shua
刷耍唰唆涮选誜選

shuai
摔甩率帅衰蟀绥卛帥綏縗缞

shuan
栓拴闩涮汕踹專栒槫腨閂

shuang
双霜爽泷孀淙傱塽孇慡樉欆滝漺瀧灀礵縔艭鏯雙騻驦骦鷞鸘鹴

shui
水谁睡税说氵娷帨挩捝氺涗涚祱稅脽裞說説誰閖

shun
顺吮瞬舜俊巛巡恂廵楯橓眴瞚瞤蕣輴順鬊

shuo
说数硕烁朔搠妁槊蒴铄嗍嗽溯濯药哾欶汋洬燿爍獡療矟碩箾萷藥說説銏鎙鑠

si
四死丝撕似私嘶思寺司斯食伺厕肆饲嗣巳耜驷兕蛳厮汜锶泗笥咝鸶姒厶缌祀澌俟以台徙析祠糸肄菥雉饴灬纟亖佀佁価俬偲傂儩凘厠噝娰媤孠廝恖愢杫枱柶梩楒榹泀泤洍涘瀃燍牭磃禗禠禩竢簛糹絲緦罒罳肂蕬蕼虒蜤螄螔蟖蟴覗謕貄逘釲鈶鈻鉰銉銯鋖鍶鐁颸飔飤飴飼駟騃騦鷉鷥麗鼶

so
螦

song
送松耸宋颂诵怂讼竦菘淞悚嵩凇崧忪锶倯傱吅娀嵷庺愯慫憁憽捒捴揔摗枀枩柗梥棇楤檧漎濍硹聳蓯蘴蜙訟誦鍶鎹頌餸駷鬆

sou
艘搜擞嗽嗾嗖飕叟薮锼馊瞍溲螋敕族涑傁凁叜廀廋捒捜摗撨擻棷櫢欶潚獀瘶籔蒐蓃藪謏鄋醙鎪鏉颼颾餿騪

su
素速诉塑宿俗苏肃粟酥缩溯僳愫簌觫稣夙嗉谡蔌涑嗖搬傃僁卹囌圱圲埣塐嫊愬憟捽摵梀棴榡樎樕橚櫯殐泝洬溸潚潥玊珟璛甦碿稡稤穌窣粛縤縮肅膆莤藗蘇蘓訴謖趚蹜遡遬鋉餗驌骕鯂鱐鷫鹔

suan
酸算蒜狻撰选匴痠祘笇筭篹選

sui
岁随碎虽穗遂尿隋髓绥隧祟眭谇濉邃燧荽睢粹莎蓑遗亗倠哸嗺埣夊娞嬘嵗挼旞檖歲歳毸浽滖澻瀡煫熣璲瓍睟砕禭穂穟簑粋綏縗繀繐繸缞脺膸芕荾葰襚誶譢賥遀遺鏸鐆鐩陏隊隨雖靃鞖韢髄

sun
孙损笋榫荪飧狲隼树跣餐喰孫巺扻損搎摌槂潠猻畃筍箰簨蓀蕵薞鎨飱鶽

suo
所缩锁琐索梭蓑莎唆挲睃嗍唢桫嗦娑羧些岁抄沙牺衰逡霍傞嗩嫅嵗惢挱摍暛歲溑溹犧獻琑瑣璅簑簔縒縮莏葰蜶褨趖逤鎈鎍鎖鎻鏁靃髿魦鮻

t

ta
他她它踏塔塌拓獭挞蹋溻趿鳎沓榻漯遢铊闼嗒太搭湿达鞑侤傝呾咜嚃嚺墖崉搨撘撻榙毾涾溚澾濌濕牠狧獺祂禢荅褟誻譶蹹躢迏迖逹達遝鉈錔鎉鎑闒闟闥阘鞈鞜鞳韃鮙鰨

tai
太抬台态胎苔泰酞汰炱肽跆呔鲐钛薹邰骀大能诒儓冭咍囼坮夳奤嬯孡忕忲態擡斄旲枱檯溙漦炲燤珆箈籉粏臺舦菭詒軚釐鈦鈶颱駘鮐

tan
谈叹探滩弹碳摊潭贪坛痰毯坦炭瘫谭坍檀袒钽郯镡锬覃澹昙忐但掸沈淡湛炎胆舔荨蕈赕倓傝僋儃啴嗿嘆嘽嘾埮墰墵壇壜婒弾彈怹惔憛憳憻撢撣擹攤暺曇榃橝歎湠漢潬灘璮痑癉癱禪緂繵罈罎舑舕菼蕁藫裧襢談譚譠貚貪賧醈醓醰鉭錟顃餤鷤黮

tang
躺趟堂糖汤塘烫倘淌唐搪棠膛螳樘羰醣瑭镗傥饧溏耥帑铴螗弹扩荡铛阊伖偒傏儻劏啺嘡坣嵣愓戃摥擴攩曭榶橖欓湯漟漡煻燙爣矘磄禟篖簜糃糛膅蓎蕩薚蘯蝪赯踼蹚逿鄌鎕鎲鏜鐋鐺钂镋閶闛闣隚鞺餳餹饄鶶黨鼞

tao
套掏逃桃讨淘涛滔陶绦萄鼗洮焘啕饕韬叨姚挑筹绸跳仐匋咷夲夵嫍幍弢慆抭搯梼槄檮涭濤燾瑫祹籌絛綢綯縚縧绹蜪裪討詜謟轁迯醄鋾錭鞀鞉鞱韜頫飸饀駣騊

te
特慝铽忑忒匿式贷犆職脦蚮螣蟘貣貸鋱

tei
忒

teng
疼腾藤誊滕僜儯幐漛痋籐籘縢膯虅螣謄邆霯駦騰驣鰧鼟

ti
提替体题踢蹄剃剔梯锑啼涕嚏惕屉醍鹈绨缇倜裼逖荑悌弟折是棣狄睇肆诋谛跃达锡扌俶偍厗啑嗁嚔奃姼媂媞屜崹嵜弚徥徲悐惖惿戻挮掦揥擿桋楴歒殢洟渧漽珶瑅瓋碮磃禵稊穉籊綈緹罤苐蕛薙虒蝭蟬衹褅褆詆諦謕趧趯踶蹏躍躰軆迏迖逷遆適銻錫鍗鐟題騠骵體髢髰鬀鬄鮧鮷鯷鳀鴺鵜鶗鶙鷈鷉鷤

tian
天田添填甜舔恬腆佃掭钿阗忝殄畋典吞嗔栝沾滇甸町苫蚕蚺锘镇颠倎兲呑唺塡娗婖寘屇悿捵搷晪沺淟湉琠瑱璳甛畇畑畠痶盷睓睼瞋碵磌窴紾緂胋舑舚菾覥觍賟酟鈿銛錪鍩鎭鎮铦闐靔靝靦顚顛餂鴫鷆鷏黇

tiao
条跳挑调迢眺龆笤祧蜩髫佻窕鲦苕粜啁姚桃稠超踔铫儵咷嬥宨岧岹庣恌斢旫晀朓朷條樤祒窱糶絩聎脁脩艞芀萔蓚蓧蓨螩覜誂調趒趠銚鋚鎥鞗頫鯈鰷齠

tie
铁贴帖萜餮占蝶锇僣呫怗惵聑蛈貼跕鉄鉆銕鋨鐡鐵飻驖鴩

ting
听停挺厅亭艇庭廷烃汀町莛铤葶婷蜓梃霆奠侱侹厛圢奵娗嵉庁庍廰廳忊桯楟榳涏渟濎烴烶珵珽筳綎耓聤聴聼聽脡艼蝏誔諪邒鋌閮鞓頲颋鼮

tiu
焞

tong
同通痛铜桶筒捅统童彤桐瞳恫侗酮潼茼仝砼峒恸佟嗵垌僮恿洞硐艟重冂偅劏勭哃囲峂峝庝慟憅晍曈朣樋橦氃浵湩炵烔熥燑爞犝狪獞痌眮硧秱穜筩粡絧統綂膧蓪蚒蜼蟲衕詷赨鉖鉵銅餇鮦鲖

tou
头偷透投钭骰亠愉绣谕谙逗偸埱妵婾媮敨斢殕紏綉緰蘣褕諭諳鋀鍮頭飳黈

tu
土图兔涂吐秃突徒凸途屠酴荼钍菟堍余杜跌兎凃唋啚図圖圗圡堗塗墿宊峹嵞嶀庩廜怢悇捈捸揬摕斁梌檡汢涋湥潳瑹痜瘏禿稌筡腞腯莵葖蒤趃跿迌釷鈯鋀鋵鍎馟駼鵌鵚鵵鶟鷋鷵鼵

tuan
团湍疃抟彖敦税鹑剬剸団圕團塼墥嫥專慱摶槫檲湪漙煓猯畽磚稅篿糰蓴褍褖貒鏄鱄鶉鷒鷻

tui
腿推退褪颓蜕煺忒弟税脱追馈侻俀僓啍墤娧尵弚怢橔稅穨聉脫脮蓷藬蘈蛻謉讉蹆蹪隤頹頺頽饋駾騩骽魋

tun
吞屯褪臀囤氽饨豚暾吨吴沌炖窀纯肫逐呑啍噋坉庉忳憞旽朜汭涒焞燉畽純膯臋芚蜳豘軘錪霕飩魨鲀黗

tuo
拖脱托妥驮拓驼椭唾鸵陀魄橐柝跎乇坨佗庹酡柁鼍沱箨砣他它惰池税舄蛇说迤铊隋舵仛侂侻咃啴嘽堶媠嫷岮彵扡拕挩捝撱杔杝棁楕槖橢毤毻汑沰涶牠狏砤碢磚稅籜紽脫舃莌萚蘀蟺袉袘袥訑託詑說説讬跅踻軃迆迱鉈鋖阤陁飥饦馱馲駄駝駞騨驒驝魠鮀鰖鱓鴕鵎鼉鼧

u

v
兡瓸瓰兝兣瓼甅兞兛瓩兙瓧瓱嗧厑旕唟莻夞巼喸唜廤蒊兺哛乲乽乤乥乫乯乺朰乭乮乶乬巪硛硳猠嚸叾仒厼穒匁丆椧焾銰浌闏囕栍虄縇襨畓屗徚曢朑桛毜毝毮烪焑燞癷稥聁艈虲蝊袰鍂鐢闧霻

w

wa
挖瓦蛙哇娃洼凹袜佤娲腽污鞋鲑劸咓唲啘嗗嗢姽媧屲帓徍搲攨汙汚溛漥瓲畖砙穵窊窐窪聉膃襪譁邷靺韈韎韤鮭黳鼃

wai
外歪崴呙夭咼喎瀤竵顡

wan
完万晚碗玩弯挽湾丸腕宛婉烷顽豌惋娩皖蔓莞脘蜿绾芄琬纨剜畹菀免关园朊箢苋贯乛倇刓卍卐唍埦塆壪夗夘妧婠孯岏帵彎忨惌抏捖捥掔晩晼杤梚椀槾汍涴潫澫灣琓盌睕笂紈絻綄綩綰翫脕莧莬萖萬薍蚖貦貫贃贎踠輐輓邜鄤鋄鋔鋺錽鍐鎫関闗關頑骩骪骫魭

wang
望忘王往网亡枉旺汪妄芒辋魍惘罔匡尢皇亾仼兦尣尩尪尫彺徃徍忹抂暀朚朢棢瀇焹琞盳網莣菵蚟蛧蝄誷輞迋迬

wei
为位未围喂胃微味尾伪威伟卫危违委魏唯维畏惟韦巍蔚谓尉潍纬慰桅萎苇渭遗葳帏艉鲔娓逶闱隈沩玮涠帷崴隗诿洧偎猥猬嵬軎韪炜煨圩薇痿倭哙囗堤岿有机熨猗眭立芟荽萏阢隹亹偉偽僞儰厃叞唩喡喴噲圍墛壝媁媙媦寪峗峞崣嵔嶶巋幃廆徫恑愄愇懀捤捼揋揻撝撱斖暐梶椲椳楲欈沇洈浘渨湋溈溦潙潿濊濰濻瀢為烓煀煒煟熭燰爲犚犩猚琟瑋璏瓗痏癐癓瞶硊硙碨磈磑維緭緯縅罻腲芛苿茟荱菋葦葨蒍蓶蔿薳藯蘶蜲蜹蜼蝛蝟螱衛衞褽覣覹觹觽觿詴諉謂讆讏趡踒踓躗躛轊違遺鄬醀錗鍏鍡鏏闈隇霨霺韋韑韙韡頠颹餧餵饖骩骪骫鮇鮠鮪鰃鰄鰖鳂鳚

wen
问文闻稳温吻蚊纹瘟紊汶阌刎雯璺免娩愠昧殁眼笏蕴限韫亠呅呚呡問塭妏彣忞忟慍抆揾搵昷桽榅榲歾殟渂溫炆煴珳瑥瘒砇穏穩紋絻緼縕缊聞肳脕脗芠莬蕰薀藴蘊蚉螡蟁褞豱輼轀辒鈫鎾閺閿闅闦韞顐饂馼魰鰛鰮鳁鳼鴍鴖鼤鞰

weng
翁嗡瓮蕹蓊壅蒙勜塕奣嵡暡滃甕瞈罋聬螉鎓鶲鹟齆

wie
膸

wo
我握窝卧挝沃蜗涡斡倭幄龌肟莴喔渥硪嗌埚夭媪杌瘟仴偓唩噁嚄堝婐婑媉媼捰捼捾撾擭枂楃涴涹渦濄濣焥猧瓁瞃矆窩腛臒臥艧萵蒦薶蝸踒踠雘馧齷龏

wu
无五屋物舞雾误捂污悟勿钨武戊务呜伍吴午吾侮乌毋恶诬芜巫晤梧坞妩蜈牾寤兀怃阢邬忤骛於鋈仵杌鹜婺迕痦芴焐庑鹉鼯浯圬亡仡侉喔垭御旄母渥瞀笏莫龉唔蝥乄亾伆俉倵儛兦剭務吳呉啎嗚噁埡堥塢墲奦娒娪娬嫵屼岉峿嵍嵨幠廡弙忢悞悮惡憮扜扝扤揾摀敄旿杅杇柮橆歍汙汚沕洖洿渞溩潕烏無熃熓玝珷珸瑦璑甒瞴矹碔祦禑窏窹箼粅膴茣莁蕪蘁螐蟱誈誣誤譕趶躌逜郚鄔釫鋘鋙錻鎢铻陚隖雺霚霧霿靰騖鯃鰞鴮鵐鵡鶩鷡鹀鼿齀齬

x

xi
西洗细吸戏系喜席稀溪熄锡膝息袭惜习嘻夕悉矽熙希檄牺晰昔媳硒铣烯腊析隙栖汐犀蜥奚浠葸饩屣玺嬉禊兮翕穸禧僖淅蓰舾蹊醯欷皙蟋羲茜徙隰唏曦螅歙樨阋粞熹觋菥鼷裼舄义咦咭屎撕既洒湿猎胁蜴褶诶谥郄错鳃郗囍係俙傒凞匸卌卥卻厀吚呬呰咥唽噏嚊嚱塈壐奊娭媐嬆宩屃屖屭嵠嶍嶲巂巇廗徆徯忔忚忥怬怸恄悕惁愾慀憘憙戯戱戲扱扸摡擊晞晳暿杫枲桸棲椞椺榽槢橀橲欪欯歖氣氥渓滊漇漝潝潟澙濕灑焁焈焟焬煕熂熈熺熻燍燨爔犔犠犧狶獡獻琋璽瓕瘜盻睎瞦矖碏磶礂稧窸糦細綌緆縘縰繥繫纚绤羛義習翖肸肹脅脇脋舃莃莔葈蒠蒵蓆蔇蕮薂虩蜤蝷螇蟢蠵衋襲覀覡覤觹觽觿訢詑誒諰謑謚謵譆谿豀豨豯貕赥赩趇趘蹝躧遟郋郤鄎酅釐釳釸鈒鈢鉨鉩銑錫錯鎴鏭鑴钑闟隟隵雟雭霫霼飁餏餙餼饻騱騽驨鬩鯑鰓鰼鱚鳛鵗鸂黖鼰鼳

xia
下吓夏峡虾瞎霞狭匣侠辖厦暇唬狎柙呷黠硖罅遐瑕假呀哧嗄嗑岈押歃毳浃瘕给葭丅俠傄叚嚇圷埉夓夾峽廈徦懗捾搳敮昰梺欱浹溊炠烚煆狹珨疜疨睱硤碬磍祫笚筪給縀縖翈舝舺芐蕸蝦螛諕謑谺赮轄郃鍜鎋鏬閕閜陜陿颬騢魻鰕鶷鎼

xian
先线县现显掀闲献嫌陷险鲜弦衔馅限咸锨仙腺贤纤宪舷涎羡铣见苋藓岘痫莶籼娴蚬猃祆冼燹跣跹酰暹氙鹇筅霰妗姗寰慊捍探洒洗濂省矣碱笕肩胁蔹轩钐锬阚黹彡仚伣伭佡俔僊僩僲僴咁咞哯唌啣嗛嘕垷埳堿壏奾妶姍姭姺娊娨娹婱嫺嫻嬐孅尟尠屳峴崄嶮幰廯忺慳憪憲憸懢挦揱搚搟撊撏攇攕晛杴枮梘槏橌櫶欦毨涀湺溓澖瀗灑灦烍狝獫獮獻玁玹珗現甉癇癎盷県睍瞯硍礆礥禒禰秈稴筧箲粯糮絃絤綅綖綫線縣縿繊纎纖缐羨羬胘脅脇脋膁臔臤臽苮莧薟藖蘚蘝蘞蚿蛝蜆衘褼襳見誢誸諴譀譣豏賢贒赻蹮躚軐軒輱醎醶釤銑銛銜鋧錎錟鍁鍌鏾鑦铦閑閒闞陥険險韅韯韱顈顕顯餡饀馦鮮鰔鱻鶱鷳鷴鷼鹹麙麲鼸

xiang
想向象项响香乡相像箱巷享镶厢降翔祥橡详湘襄飨鲞骧蟓庠芗饷缃葙亨攘洋舡亯佭傢儴勨勷啌啍嚮姠嶑廂忀晑曏栙楿欀潒珦瓖瓨絴緗纕缿羏膷萫薌蘘蚃蠁衖襐詳跭迒郷鄉鄊鄕銄銗鋞鐌鑲閧闀闂響項餉饗饟驤鬨鮝鯗鱌鱜鱶鴹麘

xiao
小笑消削销萧效宵晓肖孝硝淆啸霄哮嚣校魈蛸骁枵哓崤筱潇逍枭绡箫佼俏叟号呼咻哨唠唬姣挠捎搜梢爻狡绞胶芍茭较骄骚侾俲傚効叜呺咲啋嗃嘋嘐嘨嘮嘯嘵嚻囂婋宯庨彇恔恷憢揱撓撨敩斅斆暁曉梟橚櫹歊歒歗殽毊洨涍滧漻潚澩瀟灱灲烋焇熇熽燆燺猇獟獢痚痟皛皢睄硣穘窙笹筿箾篠簘簫絞綃縿翛脩膮莦萷蕭薂藃虈虓蟂蟏蟰蠨訤詨誟誵謏謞謼譊踃較轇郩銷颵騷驍驕骹髇髐鴞鴵鵁鷍鷕鸮

xie
写些鞋歇斜血谢卸挟屑蟹泻懈泄楔邪协械谐蝎携胁解契叶绁颉缬獬榭廨撷偕瀣渫亵榍邂薤躞燮勰唏喈接摺桔歙汁溉眭耶谍豫跬迦隰页骱鲑溃伳偞偰僁儶冩劦協卨吤嗋噧垥塮夑夾奊娎媟孈寫屓屜屟屧屭峫嶰徢恊愶慀拹挾揳搚擕擷攜旪暬枻榝槷欸殺洩湝滊潰澥瀉灺炧炨烲焎熁燲爕猲瑎碿祄禼糏紲絏絜絬綊緤緳繲纈缷翓脅脇脋膎薢藛蝑蝢蠍蠏衺裌褉褻襭觟觧諜諧謝譮讗躠鍱鐷鞢鞵韰頁頡鬹魼鮭齂齘齛齥龤

xin
新心欣信芯薪锌辛寻衅忻歆囟莘镡馨鑫昕兴款忄伈伩俽噷噺妡姰嬜孞尋庍廞惞愖憖撢杺枔橝欵歀潃炘焮盺礥脪興舋襑訢訫軐邤釁鈊鋅鐔阠顖馫馸鬵

xing
性行型形星醒姓腥刑杏兴幸邢猩惺省硎悻荥陉擤荇研胜饧侀倖哘坓坙垶塂娙婞嫈嬹巠曐洐涬滎煋熒狌瑆皨睲硏箵篂緈臖興莕蛵裄觪觲謃郉鈃鉶銒鋞钘铏陘餳騂骍鮏鯹

xiong
胸雄凶兄熊汹匈芎宪兇哅夐忷恟敻昫洶焸胷訩詗詾讻诇賯赨焽

xiu
修锈绣休羞宿嗅袖秀朽臭溴貅馐髹鸺咻庥岫煦莠俢嚊樇櫹滫烋烌珛琇璓糔綇綉繍繡脙脩臰臹苬茠蓨螑裦褎褏銝銹鎀鏅鏥鏽飍饈髤鮴鱃鵂齅

xu
许须需虚嘘蓄续序叙畜絮婿戌徐旭绪吁酗恤墟糈勖栩浒蓿顼圩洫胥醑诩溆煦盱砉于休余呕呼咻嗅姐怵旮朐肷芋规讴邪雩馘亐伃伵侐俆偦冔勗卹呴喣嘔嘼噓垿壻妶姁媭嬃幁怴恓惐慉掝揟敍敘旴昫晇暊朂楈槒欨欰欻歔歘殈汿沀淢湑滀滸漵潊烅烼獝珝珬疞盢盨眗瞁瞲矞稰稸窢籲続緒緖緰縃繻續聟胊芌芧蒣蓲蕦藇藚虗虛蚼蛡蝑規訏許訹詡諝諿謣謳譃谞賉鄦鉥銊鑐須頊驉鬚魆魖魣鱮裇

xuan
选悬旋玄宣喧轩绚眩癣券暄楦儇渲漩泫铉璇煊碹镟炫揎萱痃谖亘撰擐暖洵涓绢馔吅咺喛塇夐妶姰媗嫙嬛弲怰愃愋懁懸揈昍昡晅暅暶梋楥檈澴烜煖狟獧玆玹琁琄瑄璿瓊癬盤眴睻矎禤箮絃絢絹縣縼繏翧翾萲蓒蔙蕿藼蘐蜁蜎蝖蠉衒袨諠諼譞讂贙軒轋選還鉉鋗鍹鏇鐶镮鞙颴饌駨駽鰚

xue
学雪血靴穴削薛踅噱鳕泶决哮嚯炔谑乴勪吷坹壆學岤峃嶨怴斈桖梋樰決泧泬滈澩瀥烕燢狘疦疶瞲膤艝茓蒆袕觷謔趐轌辥雤鞾韡鱈鷽鸴辪

xun
寻讯熏训循殉旬巡迅驯汛逊勋荤询浚巽鲟浔埙恂獯醺洵郇峋蕈薰荀窨曛徇孙悛梭洒潭狻绚荨逡遁鑫彐伨侚偱勛勲勳卂咰噀噚嚑坃塤壎壦奞姰孫尋廵愻揗撏攳杊栒桪樳殾毥潯濬灥焄煇燂燅燖燻爋爓狥珣璕眴矄稄筍筼篔紃絢纁臐葷蔒蕁薫蘍蟫蟳襑訊訓訙詢賐迿遜鄩鑂顨馴駨鱏鱘鶽

y

ya
呀压牙押芽鸭轧哑亚涯丫雅衙鸦讶蚜垭疋砑琊桠睚娅痖岈氩伢迓揠厌吖吾御札歇碣辂邪闸颜鹌崖乛亜亞俹倻劜厊厓厭呾唖啞圔圠圧埡堊堐壓姶婭孲崕庌庘拁挜掗枒椏椻氬浥漄潝烏犽猚猰玡瑘疨瘂磍稏穵窫笌聐蕥襾訝軋輅輵釾錏鐚铔閘顔鴉鴨鵪鵶鶕鼼齖齾

yan
眼烟沿盐言演严咽淹炎掩厌宴岩研延堰验艳殷阉砚雁唁彦焰蜒衍谚燕颜阎铅焉奄芫厣阏菸魇琰滟焱赝筵腌兖剡餍恹罨檐湮偃谳胭晏闫俨郾酽鄢妍鼹崦阽嫣但俺厂埏埯夏巡广庵揞氤洇涎淡淫狠羡莶蔫覃讠趼这锬险靥乵偐偣傿儼兗円剦匽厃厭厳厴唌喦喭噞嚥嚴囐塩墕壛壧夵妟姲姸娫娮媕嬊嬐嬮嬿孍屵崄嵃嵒嵓嶖嶮巌巖巗巘巚廵弇彥愝懕戭扊抁挩挻捝掞揅揜敥昖晻暥曕曮棪椻椼楌樮橪檿櫩欕殗沇洝淊渰渷湺溎漹灎灔灧灩炏烻焔煙熖燄爓牪狿猒珚琂瓛甗硏硯硽碞礹篶簷綖縯羨膁臙艶艷莚菴萒葊葕蔅薟虤蝘裺褗覎觃觾訁訮詽諺讌讞豓豔豜豣贋贗躽軅這遃郔酀酓醃醶醼釅鉛錟閆閹閻閼阭陰隁隒險靨顏顑顔顩饜騐験騴驗驠鬳魘鰋鳫鳱鴈鴳鶠鷃鷰鹽麙麣麲黡黤黫黬黭黰黶鼴齗齞齴龂龑啱

yang
样养羊洋仰扬秧氧痒杨漾阳殃央鸯佯疡炀恙徉鞅泱蛘烊怏昂映英详佒傟劷勜卬咉坱垟奍姎婸將岟崵崸慃懩抰揚攁敭旸昜暘柍楊楧様樣歍氜氱湯潒瀁炴煬珜瑒瘍癢眏眻礢禓紻羏羕羘羪胦詇詳諹軮輰鉠鍈鍚鐊钖阦陽雵霙霷颺飏飬養駚鰑鴦鴹鸉

yao
要摇药咬腰窑舀邀妖谣遥姚瑶耀尧钥侥陶约疟珧夭鳐鹞轺爻吆铫幺崾肴曜徭杳窈么乐啮娆幼洮淫瀹由繇荛骜仸倄偠傜僥匋喓嗂噛嚙垚堯婹媱嬈宎尭岆峣嶢嶤徺怮恌愮抭揺搖摿撽暚曣枖柼楆榚榣樂殀殽溔滛烄烑熎燿狕猶猺獟玅瑤眑矅磘祅穾窅窔窯窰筄箹約纅艞苭葯葽蓔蕘薬藥蘨袎覞訞詏謠謡讑趯踰軺遙銚鎐鑰闄隃靿顤颻飖餆餚騕驁鰩鴁鴢鷂鷕鼼齩

ye
也夜业野叶爷页液掖腋冶噎耶咽曳椰邪谒邺晔烨揶铘靥喝墅射拽揞揲斜洇涂聂荼馀亪亱倻偞僷吔啘嘢嚈埜堨墷壄峫嶪嶫懕抴捓捙擖擛擨擪擫暍曄曅曗枒枼枽楪業歋殕殗洂漜潱澲煠熀燁爗爺瓛痷皣瞱瞸礏窫緤聶葉虵蠮蠱謁鄓鄴釶釾鋣鍱鎁鎑鐷靨頁餘餣饁饐馌驜鵺鸈黦

yen
岃膶

yi
一以已亿衣移依易医乙仪亦椅益倚姨翼译伊蛇遗食艾胰疑沂宜异彝壹蚁谊揖铱矣翌艺抑绎邑蛾屹尾役臆逸肄疫颐裔意毅忆义夷溢诣议怿痍镒癔怡驿旖熠酏翊欹峄圯殪嗌咦懿噫劓诒饴漪佚咿瘗猗眙羿弈苡荑仡佾贻钇缢迤刈悒黟翳弋奕蜴埸挹嶷薏呓轶镱舣丿也佗印台叹听噎圪坨夕失奇姬它射崎巳怠择掎搋施汽治泄洫渫焉焱熙犄疙硪绁绮维羡衤袂诶谥迭释铊隶雉黝乁乂亄伇伿佁侇俋偯儀億儗兿冝劮勚勩匇匜叆叕吚呭呹唈囈圛坄垼埶墿壱夁妷媐嫕嫛嬄嬑嬟孴宐宧寱寲峓崺嶧嶬巸帟帠幆庡廙弌弬彛彜彞彵忔怈恞悘悥憶懌戺扅扆扡拸掜搤撎擇攺敡敼斁旑昳晹暆曀曎曵杙杝枍枻柂栘栧栺桋棭椬椸榏槷槸樴檍檥檹櫂欥欭歖歝殔殹毉沶泆洢洩浂浥浳湙潩澤澺瀷炈焬焲熈熤熪熼燚燡燱狋狏獈玴珆瑿瓵畩異痬瘞瘱睪瞖礒礙祎禕秇稦穓竩笖箷簃籎紲絏維綺縊繄繶繹羛羠羨義耛耴肊膉艗艤芅苅苢萓萟蓺藙藝蘙虉蛜蛡蛦螔螘螠蟻衪衵袆袘袣裛裿褘褹襗襼觺訑訲訳詍詑詒詣誃誒誼謚謻譩譯議譺讉讛豙豛豷貖貤貽賹贀跇跠踦軼輗輢轙辥辷迆迱迻逘遺郼醫醳醷釋釔釴釶鈘鈠鉇鉈鉯銕銥錡鎰鏔鐿钀锜阣阤陁陭隿霅霬靉靾頉頤頥顊顗飴饐駅驛骮鮧鮨鯣鳦鴺鶂鶃鶍鷁鷊鷖鷧鷾鸃鹝鹢鹥黓黳齮齸

yin
因引印银音饮阴隐荫吟尹寅茵淫殷姻烟堙鄞喑夤胤龈吲圻狺垠霪蚓氤铟窨瘾洇茚众听垦壹币沂浔潭芩言廴湮乑乚伒侌傿冘凐唫噖噾嚚囙圁垔垽堷婣婬峾崟崯嶾廕愔慇慭憖憗懚斦朄栶梀檃檭檼櫽欭欽歅殥泿洕淾湚溵滛潯濥濦烎犾猌玪珢璌瘖癊癮硍碒磤禋秵筃粌絪緸縯苂荶蒑蔩蔭蘟螾蟫裀訔訚訡訢誾諲讔赺趛輑酓酳釿鈏鈝銀銦闇闉阥陰陻隂隠隱霒霠靷鞇韾飮飲駰骃鮣鷣齗齦龂

ying
应硬影营迎映蝇赢鹰英颖莹盈婴樱缨荧萤萦楹蓥瘿茔鹦媵莺璎郢嘤撄瑛滢潆嬴罂瀛膺荥颍哽央景甸绳逞俓偀僌啨営噟嚶塋夃媖嫈嬰孆孾嵤巆巊廮応愥應摬攍攖攚旲暎朠柍桜桯梬櫻櫿泂浧渶溁溋滎潁濙濚濴瀅瀠瀯瀴灐灜焸煐熒營珱瑩瓔甇甖癭盁眏矨碤礯穎籝籯緓縄縈繩纓绬罃罌耺膡莖萾藀蘡蛍蝧蝿螢蠅蠳褮覮謍譍譻賏贏軈鎣鐛鑍锳霙鞕韹韺頴颕鱦鴬鶧鶯鷪鷹鸎鸚焽鶑

yo
哟育唷喲嚛

yong
用涌永拥蛹勇雍咏泳佣踊痈庸臃恿壅慵俑墉鳙邕喁甬饔镛容臾蕹遇傛傭勈嗈噰埇塎嫞嵱廱彮怺悀惥愑愹慂揘擁柡栐槦湧滽澭灉牅癕癰砽硧禜筩苚蒏詠踴郺鄘醟銿鏞雝顒颙鯒鰫鱅鲬鷛

you
有又由右油游幼优友铀忧尤犹诱悠邮酉佑釉幽疣攸蚰莠鱿卣黝莸猷蚴宥牖囿柚蝣莜鼬铕蝤繇呦侑叹坳奥尢扰揄泅聱锈丣亴偤優冘哊唀嚘妋姷孧尣峟峳庮怞怣怮憂懮戭揂斿栯梄梎楢槱櫌櫾汓汼沋泈泑浟湵滺瀀牗牰狖猶獶甴痏祐禉秞糿纋羐羑羗耰聈肬脜脩苃莤蒏蕕蚘蜏褎褏訧誘貁輏輶迶逌逰遊邎郵鄾酭鈾銪銹駀魷鮋鲉麀

yu
与于欲鱼雨余遇语愈狱玉渔予誉育愚羽虞娱淤舆屿禹宇迂俞逾域芋郁谷吁盂喻峪御愉粥渝尉榆隅浴寓裕预豫驭蔚妪嵛雩馀阈窬鹆妤揄窳觎臾舁龉蓣煜钰谀纡於竽瑜禺聿欤俣伛圄鹬庾昱萸瘐谕鬻圉瘀熨饫毓燠腴狳菀蜮蝓亏吾唷喁噢夕奥宛崛懊或拗昙栩梧污汩澳煨王腧舒苑菸蜍衙阏肀丂亐伃俁俼偊傴僪儥兪匬叞吳唹喅喐喩噊噳圫堉堣堬墺娛娪娯婾媀媮嫗嬩寙峿崳嵎嶎嶼庽彧忬悆悇惌惐慾懙戫扜扵挧捓敔斔斞旟杅栯桙棛棜棫楀楡楰櫲欎欝歈歟歶汙汚淢淯湡滪漁澚澞澦灪灹焴燏燰爩牏獄獝玗玙琙琟瑀璵畬畭痏瘉癒盓睮矞砡硢礇礖礜祤禦秗稢稶穥穻箊篽籅籞籲紆緎繘罭羭翑與艅芌茟茰荢萭萮蒮蓹蕍蕷薁藇蘌蘛虶蜟蝺螸蟈衘衧袬褕覦語諛諭謣譽貍貐貗踰軉輍輿轝迃逳遹邘郚鄅酑醧釪鈺銉鋊鋙錥鍝鐍鐭铻閼閾陓隃隩雓霱預頨顒颙飫餘饇馭騟驈骬髃鬰鬱魊魚魣鮽鯲鰅鱊鱮鳿鴥鴧鴪鵒鷠鷸鸆鸒麌齬齵

yuan
远员元院圆原愿园援猿怨冤源缘袁渊苑垣鸳辕圜鼋橼媛爰眢鸢掾芫沅瑗螈箢塬垸允咽宛捐涓穿阮陨傆剈厡厵員喛噮囦圎園圓夗妧妴媴嫄嫚嬽寃弲悁惌杬棩楥榞榬櫞涴淵渁渆渕湲溒灁焆猨獂盶禐笎緣縁羱肙葾蒝蒬薗薳蚖蜎蜵蝝蝯衏裫裷褑褤謜貟贠輐轅逺遠邍邧酛鈨鋺鎱隕願駌騵魭鳶鴛鵷鶢鶰鹓黿鼘鼝茒

yue
月越约跃阅乐岳悦曰说粤钥瀹钺刖龠栎樾哕囝块妁烁药蜕蠖跞铄锐哾噦妜嬳岄嶽彟彠恱悅戉扚抈捳擽曱枂櫟汋焆爍爚玥矆矱礿禴箹篗籆籥籰粵約臒蘥蚎蚏蛻說説趯跀躍躒軏鈅鉞銳鋭鑠閱閲髺鸑鸙黦龥

yun
云运晕允匀韵陨孕耘蕴酝郧员氲恽愠郓芸筠韫昀狁殒纭熨均媪尉尹怨温瘟盾苑菀伝傊勻叞呍員喗囩夽奫妘媼惲愪慍抎抣暈枟榅樂橒殞氳沄涒涢溳澐煇煴煾熅熉玧畇眃磒秐筍筼篔紜緷緼縕縜繧缊耺腪荺蒀蒕蒷蕓蕰薀藴蘊蜵蝹褞貟賱贇贠赟輼轀辒運鄆鄖醖醞鈗鋆阭隕雲霣韗韞韻頵餫馧馻齫齳鞰

z

za
杂砸咋匝扎咱咂拶啐嘁籴啈喒噈囃囋囐帀桚沞沯濽灒磼紥紮臜臢襍鉔雑雜雥韴魳

zai
在再灾载栽宰哉甾崽仔才傤儎扗洅渽溨災烖睵縡菑賳載酨岾

zan
咱暂攒赞簪趱糌瓒拶昝錾涔湔偺儧儹兂喒囋寁揝撍攢暫桚濺濽灒瓉瓚禶穳篸簮臢襸讃讚賛贊趲蹔鄼酂酇鏨鏩鐕鐟饡

zang
脏葬赃藏奘臧驵戕匨塟弉牂牫羘臓臟蔵賍賘贓贜銺駔驡髒

zao
早造遭糟灶燥枣凿躁藻皂噪澡蚤唣槽窖缫缲草傮唕喿慥栆梍棗煰璅璪皁竃竈簉繅繰艁薻謲譟趮蹧醩鑿

ze
则责择泽咋侧箦舴帻迮啧仄昃笮赜厕措柞稷谪伬側則厠唶啫嘖夨嫧崱幘庂廁択捑擇昗樍歵汄沢泎溭滜澤灂皟睪瞔矠礋稄簀耫萚葃蔶蘀蠌襗諎謫謮讁責賾飵鸅齚齰

zei
贼鲫蠈賊鯽鰂鱡鲗

zen
怎谮僭囎撍譖譛

zeng
增赠憎曾综缯罾甑锃増曽橧熷璔矰磳綜縡繒譄贈鄫鋥鬷鱛

zh

zha
扎炸渣闸眨榨乍轧诈铡札蜡查栅咋砟痄吒哳楂猹蚱揸喋柞咤齄册哆怍插渫笮膪苴鲽龃馇喳偞偧冊剳劄厏喥囃奓宱扠抯拃挓挿揷搩搾摣擖柤柵樝溠潳灹煠牐甴皶皻箑箚紥紮耫苲蔖蕏藸蚻觰詐諎謯譇譗踷蹅軋迊醡鍘閘霅鞢鮓鮺鰈鲊鲝齇齟齰

zhai
摘窄债斋寨择翟宅侧祭砦瘵度柴疵箦膪责骀亝側債厇厏啇嚌夈抧捚擇擿斎榸檡牴簀粂責鉙駘骴齋

zhan
站占战盏沾粘毡展栈詹颤蘸湛绽斩辗崭瞻谵搌旃湔澶袒谦躔醮骣亶佔偡噡嫸嵁嶃嶄嶘嶦怗惉戦戰拃斬旜栴桟棧椾榐橏欃氈氊琖皽盞碊綻菚薝虥虦蛅襢覱詀謙譧譫讝趈跕蹍輚輾轏邅醆閚霑颭飐飦餰饘驏驙魙鱣鳣鳽鸇鹯點黵

zhang
张章长帐仗丈掌涨账樟杖彰漳胀瘴障仉嫜幛鄣璋嶂獐蟑承仧傽墇帳幥弡張慞扙暲涱漲痮瘬瞕礃粀粻脹蔁賬遧鏱鐣長镸鞝餦騿鱆麞

zhao
找着照招罩爪兆朝昭沼肇嘲召赵棹啁钊笊诏晁桃淖濯著蚤佋啅垗妱巶旐曌枛櫂炤燳爫狣瑵皽盄瞾窼箌罀羄肁肈菬詔謿趙釗釽鉊鍣駋鮡鳭鼂鼌

zhe
着这者折遮蛰哲蔗锗辙浙柘辄赭摺鹧磔褶蜇谪乇嗫嘀堵庶摄斥耷聂褚轶陬鸷著仛厇啠喆嗻嚞囁埑嫬悊慹扸摂攝晢晣杔棏樀樜歽淛潪矺砓籷粍聑聶虴蟄蟅袩襵詟謫謶謺讁讋軼輒輙轍這適銸鍺馲驝鮿鷓鷙

zhei
这這

zhen
真阵镇针震枕振斟珍疹诊甄砧臻贞侦缜蓁祯箴轸榛稹赈朕鸩胗浈桢畛圳椹唇坫填慎戡溱滇趁鲞鼎帧侲偵塡塦姫嫃寊屒帪弫抮挋揕搸敒敶昣朾枮栕栚桭楨榐槇樼殝沴沵湞潧澵獉珎瑧眕眞眹碪禎禛竧籈紖紾絼縝縥纼聄萙葴蒖薽蜄袗裖覙診誫謓貞賑趂軫轃辴迧遉酖酙針鈂鉁鋴錱鍖鍼鎭鎮陣陳靕駗鬒鮝鱵鴆黮黰鼑

zheng
正整睁争挣征怔证症郑拯丁蒸狰政峥钲铮筝诤徵鲭丞伥承敞止町瞠趟帧佂倀凧埥埩塣姃媜崝崢嶒幀徎徰徴愸憕抍掙掟揁撜晸氶浧湞炡烝爭猙癥眐睜箏篜糽綪聇脀証諍證踭鄭鉦錚鬇鮏鯖鯹鴊

zhi
只之直知制指纸支芝枝稚吱蜘质肢脂汁炙织职痔植抵殖执值侄址滞止趾治旨窒志挚掷至致置帜识峙氏智秩帙摭黹桎枳轵忮祉蛭膣觯郅栀彘芷祗咫鸷絷踬胝骘轾痣陟踯雉埴贽卮酯豸跖栉伎埃多实徵恃拓昵栽氐示祁积耆迟郦铁鸠夂乿亊俧倁値偫傂儨凪剬劕劧厔咥嚔坁坧垁執墆墌夛妷姪娡媞嬂寘實崻巵帋幟庢庤廌徏徔徝徴恉慹憄懥懫戠扺扻抧拞挃捗搘搱摕摨摯擲擳擿斦旘晊杝杫柣栺梔梽椥楖榰槜樀樲樴櫍櫛歭汥汦沚泜洔洷淽滍滯漐潌潪瀄熫犆狾猘瓆瓡畤疐疷疻瘈眰砋礩祇祑祬禃禔禵秇秓秖秪秲秷稙稺穉筫紙紩絺綕緻縶織翐聀職胑胵膱臷臸芖茋茝菭薙藢蘵虒蚔螲蟙衹衼袟袠製襧覟觗觝觶訨誌謢識豑豒貭質贄跱踶蹛蹠蹢躑躓軄軹軽輊迣遟遲酈釞鉄銍銴鋕鑕铚锧阤阯陁隲隻馶馽駤騭騺驇鯯鳩鳷鴙鴲鶨鷙鼅

zhong
中重种钟肿众终盅忠仲衷踵舯螽锺冢忪潼童舂董蚣夂乑伀偅刣喠堹塚妐妕媑尰幒彸徸柊歱汷泈炂煄狆瘇眾祌種穜筗籦終緟腫茽蔠蚛蝩螤蟲衆衳衶褈諥蹱迚鈆鈡銿鍾鐘鴤鼨

zhou
周洲皱粥州轴舟昼骤宙诌肘帚咒繇胄纣荮啁碡绉籀妯酎侏倜啄喙府扭柚注祝舳诹调逐铀驺鬻伷侜僽冑呪咮喌噣嚋婤徟掫晝晭椆洀淍炿烐珘甃疛皺盩睭矪箒籒籕粙紂紬縐翢胕菷葤薵詋詶調諏謅譸诪賙赒軸輈輖辀週郮鈾銂霌駎駲騆騶驟鯞鵃鸼

zhu
住主猪竹株煮筑贮铸嘱拄注祝驻属术珠瞩蛛朱柱诸诛逐助烛蛀潴洙伫瘃翥茱苎橥舳杼箸炷侏铢疰渚褚躅麈邾槠竺予宁庶斗朝柠楮泞澍茁蚰逗阻除驺著丶佇劅劚劯咮嗻噣囑坾墸壴孎宔尌屬嵀搊敱斀斸曯枓柷樦櫡櫧櫫欘殶泏濐瀦灟炢煑燭爥眝矚砫硃磩祩秼窋竚笁笜筯築篫篴紵紸絑纻罜羜芧苧茿莇蓫蕏薥藷藸蝫蠋蠩蠾袾註詝誅諸豬貯跓跙跦軴迬逫鉏鉒銖鋳鑄钃陼霔飳馵駐駯騶鮢鯺鱁鴸鸀麆鼄

zhua
抓爪挝摣撾檛簻膼髽

zhuai
拽转嘬尵捙睉跩顡

zhuan
转专砖赚传撰篆颛馔啭沌抟湍傳僎僝剸叀囀堟塼嫥孨専專恮摶漙灷瑑瑼甎磚竱篹篿簨籑縳耑腞膞蒃蟤襈諯譔賺転轉鄟顓饌鱄磗

zhuang
装撞庄壮桩状幢妆僮奘戆丬憧艟赣壯壵妝娤庒戅戇梉樁湷漴焋狀獞粧糚荘莊裝贑贛

zhui
追坠缀锥赘椎骓惴缒隹垂揣槌致萑隧倕埀墜娷沝甀畷硾磓礈笍箠綴縋腏膇諈贅轛醀醊錐錗錣鎚鑆隊餟騅鵻

zhun
准谆屯肫窀淳盹纯胗饨凖啍圫埻宒忳旽湻準甽稕純綧衠訰諄迍飩黱

zhuo
捉桌着啄拙灼浊卓琢缴茁酌擢焯濯诼浞涿倬镯禚斫勺啜掇棹淖箸肫蕞趵踔躅杓著丵剢劅叕啅噣圴坧墌妰娺彴捔撯擆斀斮斱斲斵晫梲棁棳椓槕櫡汋準濁灂炪烵犳狵琸矠硺穛穱窡窧篧籗籱繳罬聉蓔藋蝃蠗蠿諁諑謶趠蹠鉵鋜鐯鐲鵫鷟

zi
字自子紫籽资姿吱滓仔兹咨孜渍滋淄笫粢龇秭恣谘趑缁梓鲻锱孳耔觜髭赀茈訾嵫眦姊辎事呲次甾疵载锌齐倳剚吇呰啙嗞姉姕孖孶崰杍栥椔榟橴沝泚洓湽漬澬牸玆璾眥矷禌秄秶稵穧紎緇胏胔胾芓茊茡茲菑葘蓻薋虸訿諮貲資赼趦跐載輜輺鄑釨鈭鋅錙鍿鎡镃頾頿鯔鰦鶅鼒齊齍齜嗭

zong
总纵宗棕综踪鬃偬粽枞腙倊倧傯堫嵏嵕嵸從惣惾愡捴揔搃摠昮朡椶樅潀潈潨熜熧燪猔猣疭瘲碂磫稯糉綜緃総緫緵縂縦縱總翪艐葼蓗蓯蝬豵踨蹤錝鍯鏓鑁騌騣骔鬉鬷鯮鯼

zou
走揍奏邹鲰鄹陬驺诹族楱辶偢媰掫搊棷棸箃緅芻菆諏赱郰鄒騶鯐鯫黀齱齺

zu
组族足阻租祖诅菹镞卒俎啐嘁徂沮淬苴趱蹴驵伜伹倅傶卆哫岨崒崪怚柤爼珇砠稡箤紣組綷葅蒩詛謯趲踤踿鉃鉏鉐錊鎐鎺鏃鑿靻顇駔唨

zuan
钻纂赚缵躜攥撮攒劗揝攢欑篹籫繤纉纘賺躦鑚鑽

zui
最嘴醉罪堆咀觜蕞摧撮羧厜嗺噿嫢嶉嶊嶵晬朘枠栬槯樶檇檌欈濢璻睟祽稡穝絊纗脧蟕辠酔酨酻鋷錊雋

zun
尊遵鳟撙樽奠蹲僎僔噂墫嶟拵捘捽栫瀳繜罇袸譐跧踆銌鐏鱒鶎鷷

zuo
做作坐左座昨凿琢撮佐笮酢唑祚胙怍阼柞乍挫砟醋嘬阝侳咗岝岞捽柮椊秨稓筰糳繓苲莋葃葄蓙袏諎鈼鑿飵咗




